<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-27T21:23:05.507" Score="7" ViewCount="67" Body="&lt;p&gt;While answering a few of &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/8/edchum&quot;&gt;EdChum&lt;/a&gt;'s questions I discovered that what I/we in the USA call pour over coffee is referred to as drip coffee in the UK. I added the pour-over tag to both questions I encountered but figured we should decide as a community which tag to use to describe this brewing process and then properly document it because drip-coffee means something different in the US (which is apparently referred to as filter-cofee in the UK). For clarification the method in question is shown in the image below. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/8BYnT.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="24" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:53:35.523" Title="Should we describe the process of brewing a single cup via pouring water over ground coffee as pour-over-coffee or drip-coffee?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-27T21:26:10.227" Score="5" ViewCount="44" Body="&lt;p&gt;Being newly created we have zero feeds appearing in our main chat right now. What blogs, news sites, or other important coffee related things should appear in our main chat room's feed? Post your suggestions/submissions.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="24" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-01-28T15:23:57.013" LastActivityDate="2015-02-06T14:14:32.833" Title="What should go in our main chat feeds?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-27T21:30:20.953" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;It looks like filter coffee has &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indian_filter_coffee&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;another, different meaning&lt;/a&gt; too. When I read &quot;drip coffee,&quot; I think of the kind you &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Drip_brew&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;get from a traditional coffeemaker&lt;/a&gt;. Go for &quot;pour-over.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="3" LastActivityDate="2015-01-27T21:30:20.953" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="7" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:31:45.837" Score="15" ViewCount="197" Body="&lt;p&gt;The chatroom name is so bland. &quot;Coffee.&quot; Look at all the creative names others have thought up:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;Root Access&quot; for Super User&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The DMZ&quot; for Security&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The Renderfarm&quot; for Blender&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The Litter Box&quot; for Pets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The Hangar&quot; for Aviation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;You Are Here&quot; for Travel&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The Water Cooler&quot; for The Workplace&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The Whiteboard&quot; for Programmers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The Nineteenth Byte&quot; for Code Golf&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;etc...&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can we think of a better name for our chatroom?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Only one idea per answer, please. Vote up the ideas that you like!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;Stolen from &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.lifehacks.stackexchange.com/q/25/88&quot;&gt;Lifehacks meta&lt;/a&gt;, which was in turn stolen from &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.codegolf.stackexchange.com/q/1005/3808&quot;&gt;PPCG meta&lt;/a&gt;. But that's okay, because I wrote both of those posts too. :P&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="63" LastActivityDate="2015-02-11T23:36:17.020" Title="Let's think of a creative name for our chatroom" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;chat&gt;" AnswerCount="18" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="10" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:34:21.017" Score="6" ViewCount="95" Body="&lt;p&gt;On most SE sites, product recommendations are off-topic, as they tend to become obsolete quickly (see &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/11/qa-is-hard-lets-go-shopping/&quot;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;). Do we want questions asking for the recommendation of goods/products here?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do we want to completely rule recomendations off-topic, or should we allow certain kinds?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="59" LastActivityDate="2015-02-09T23:08:30.040" Title="Should product recommendations be on-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:35:17.573" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;In the UK and Japan we refer to these:&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/l6bTs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;as drip coffee this is a fairly recent thing to invade UK espresso shops but they have been around for a while in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whilst this:&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/Wje9f.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;is what we call filter coffee. I'm happy to use both terms but this could turn territorial perhaps as it's unclear what the correct term should be as this is not just a UK-ism.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It may be better to just have a tag synonym in this case perhaps?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just to defend my corner a little &lt;a href=&quot;http://hario.co.uk/search?type=product&amp;amp;q=drip&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;hario&lt;/a&gt; is one of the main sellers of these kinds of products and they seem to be the main brand in use in UK and you can see that drip is the term used in their products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And again here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hario.co.jp/coffee/hario_coffee/dripdecanter.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.hario.co.jp/coffee/hario_coffee/dripdecanter.html&lt;/a&gt; although the page is in japanese the url itself uses the term drip.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8" LastEditorUserId="8" LastEditDate="2015-01-27T23:05:27.840" LastActivityDate="2015-01-27T23:05:27.840" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:38:09.300" Score="12" Body="&lt;h1&gt;The Percolator&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4" LastEditorUserId="127" LastEditDate="2015-02-03T09:51:37.103" LastActivityDate="2015-02-03T09:51:37.103" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:47:01.130" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;The Coffee Break&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not exactly a thing as much as a time, but take it for what it's worth...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2015-01-27T22:47:01.130" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:48:28.107" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;The Brewing Station&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another idea that might work...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2015-01-27T22:48:28.107" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:53:17.090" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;One inherent problem of product recommendations is that they are very attractive to spammers. With just a little effort it's hard to differentiate between spam and a well-meant and thoroughly researched recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally they can be highly subjective and to top it all off, they have to meet certain requirements to be reasonably answered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This all leads me to the conclusion, that product recommendations should be off-topic for this site. One can always ask for personal opinions in chat :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46" LastActivityDate="2015-01-27T22:53:17.090" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="11" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-27T22:56:05.857" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;'The coffee-mill' - grinding ourselves a coffee here &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="46" LastActivityDate="2015-01-27T22:56:05.857" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="12" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-27T23:07:16.797" Score="10" ViewCount="82" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/43/how-to-prevent-calcium-loss-when-drinking-a-lot-of-coffee&quot;&gt;How to prevent calcium loss when drinking a lot of coffee?&lt;/a&gt; has shown up and while its certainly coffee related I am unsure if A) any and all health related queries would really be on topic and B) if we as a community could truly be said to possess enough expertise on biochemistry and health practices to adequately answer said questions even if the first condition is true. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="24" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T12:52:13.503" Title="Should health related questions be off topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="12" CreationDate="2015-01-27T23:19:00.887" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would vote no. But to be fair I assume there's doctors out there who drink coffee that may actually know about this. That and there must be scientific articles somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="57" LastActivityDate="2015-01-27T23:19:00.887" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="14" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="44" CreationDate="2015-01-27T23:23:35.603" Score="7" ViewCount="60" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've seen a post asking about the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/53/how-v60-and-aeropress-affect-flavor&quot;&gt;flavor of coffee&lt;/a&gt;. As a food site, these questions will certainly end up in the private beta. These questions may be subjective (what is sweet to one is bitter to another), but I don't know if we should just close all questions of this type.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="87" LastEditorUserId="87" LastEditDate="2015-01-28T03:13:25.933" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T22:31:59.327" Title="How should questions about coffee flavor be handled?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="15" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2015-01-28T00:36:20.557" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;This was my concern with an answer I gave a few minutes ago. I wanted to make the asker aware of a product, but didn't want to get shut down for anything that looked like spamming. I chose to provide a link to the manufacturer's &quot;features&quot; page, which lacked any way to buy the product. Another question had an excellent answer that provided links to purchase the equipment the asker would need to do what they were asking about (backflushing their espresso machine).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Product recommendations can be made from an honest place, but (as has been said) whether a particular post is inappropriate is very subjective. If product recommendations are off-topic, where is the line?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="91" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T00:36:20.557" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="16" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="18" CreationDate="2015-01-28T00:44:38.967" Score="2" ViewCount="37" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are questions that asked stuff like how should you store coffee beans and stuff where answers may vary. One of my questions was that whether coffee should be served warm or hot. That question was similar, except with only two possible choices. Yet a user says that my question is opinion-based. Now I am confused on what types of questions will be opinion-based. So my question is, which types of questions would be considered opinion-based?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="75" LastEditDate="2015-01-28T00:52:56.010" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:30:33.230" Title="What Will Be Considered Opinion Based" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;support&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="17" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2015-01-28T01:19:58.597" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Giving specific recommendations (eg. brand names) should be avoided. Not only is it hard to distinguish legitimate recommendations from product promotions and other spam, but these sorts of things are inherently opinion based (which is generally discouraged on SE sits).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;General recommendations (eg. recommending a french press to achieve a certain kind of flavor), is a different matter, of course and may be necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:19:58.597" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="18" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2015-01-28T01:30:33.230" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;What flavor is &quot;preferable&quot;, strikes me as primarily opinion based. However, asking about the general types of coffee flavors should be encouraged. When describing a flavor or taste there are going to be some adjectives that may not be viewed the same way by everyone reading them. If one person says a coffee is &quot;bitter&quot;, that's not necessarily opinion based. Saying that &quot;because it's bitter it is no good&quot;, however, is.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's hard to mark a defining line, but it's a line that we can define as a community, and shouldn't try to pin down right away (though, for the most part, I think it will be fairly obvious when someone crosses it).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other examples:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Opinion based&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A robusta is &lt;strong&gt;better&lt;/strong&gt; than an arabica&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do you &lt;strong&gt;prefer&lt;/strong&gt; a french press or a pour-over?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bitter coffee's taste bad&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Not opinion based&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This coffee has a bitter aftertaste&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Coffee &lt;em&gt;A&lt;/em&gt; is more bitter than coffee &lt;em&gt;B&lt;/em&gt; (somewhat opinion based, but how else do you describe it when making a comparison? this really depends on the question, I think)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:30:33.230" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="20" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="21" CreationDate="2015-01-28T01:36:49.147" Score="3" ViewCount="50" Body="&lt;p&gt;I posted &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/89/how-does-the-altitude-at-which-beans-are-grown-affect-the-final-roast?noredirect=1#comment81_89&quot;&gt;a question&lt;/a&gt; about coffee growing, and asked what mechanisms affect the flavor of coffee grown at different altitudes (I was thinking of things like temperature, wind, soil differences, etc. might come up).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At least one person suggested that this second part of the question (about what mechanisms cause flavor differences if altitude does indeed affect the final product) was &quot;too scientific&quot; and suggested that it be closed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does this mean all growing questions should be off topic? Or all questions related to the chemistry or biology of coffee? Where do we draw the line?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:39:32.123" Title="Are questions about growing coffee beans on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="21" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="20" CreationDate="2015-01-28T01:39:32.123" Score="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;My personal opinion is that this site should be for coffee growers, roasters, and drinkers alike and that somewhat &quot;scientific&quot; questions should be perfectly on topic as long as they pertain more to coffee than the science.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions about the biology of a coffee bean probably belong elsewhere (as they are more about biology and could probably apply to any bean), questions about how some chemical process affects the final flavor of coffee, probably belong here (as it's something a coffee expert could probably answer better than a general chemistry expert).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TL;DR — If a &lt;em&gt;coffee&lt;/em&gt; expert could answer it better than a &lt;em&gt;insert-branch-of-science-here&lt;/em&gt; expert, it's probably a better fit here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:39:32.123" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="23" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="14" CreationDate="2015-01-28T01:48:54.133" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;It may depend. If they are asking something like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is It Preferred To Have Flavor A or Flavor B&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That will be subjective and primarily opinion-based as every one has their favorite choice. But if the question is something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Will This Affect The Flavor of The Coffee&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That will not be subjective due to the fact it is just asking of the flavor will change or not. This is the situation with the question you posted. The asker just wants to see how the flavor will change, not which one is the best and why. I hope this answers your question!   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:48:54.133" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="24" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-28T01:53:35.523" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/pour-over&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'pour-over'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;pour-over&lt;/a&gt; is the best tag for the job, simply because it will not be confused with another method. If you call it &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/drip-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'drip-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;drip-coffee&lt;/a&gt;, then one locale will try to apply the tag to one method of brewing, while another locale will use a different one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If we then call the machine method &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/filter-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'filter-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;filter-coffee&lt;/a&gt;, and discourage the use of &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/drip-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'drip-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;drip-coffee&lt;/a&gt;, it makes for less ambiguity. Admittedly, it does make it difficult for the nationalities who don't use those terms, but I think that's better than having half the people on here tagging with one and half the other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TL;DR — I think we should use &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/pour-over&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'pour-over'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;pour-over&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/filter-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'filter-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;filter-coffee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T01:53:35.523" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="25" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T03:49:37.673" Score="-4" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;Stackbucks Coffee&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sorry, that was too tempting... I like the chatty aspect, though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="98" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T03:49:37.673" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T07:20:05.917" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;just &quot;café&quot; ... &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Above the line is my answer. The rest is just filler to fulfill minimum length criterion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="119" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T07:20:05.917" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="27" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="12" CreationDate="2015-01-28T07:23:48.043" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;Coffee is not simply a food, but a beverage with phisiological and neurological effects, that are the main reason many (most?) people drink it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So it's quite natural that the way the coffee works on human body should be on topic there.  At least in my opinion. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T07:23:48.043" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="28" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-28T07:27:33.803" Score="4" ViewCount="85" Body="&lt;p&gt;as a nascent community, we like to grow as well as have an identity. A Logo carry a lot about the identity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We should start think, brew, and sketch the ideas. Even you can contribute your not-so-polished design.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IMO, A logo should be simple, unique, meaningful and fun. What do you think ?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="119" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-01-28T15:23:23.557" LastActivityDate="2015-02-16T13:56:00.227" Title="What logo we can have ? Let's start working" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;logo&gt;&lt;identity&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="29" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T07:49:03.007" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Coffehouse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since a coffeehouse is where you take a break and have a chat. So my vote goes for &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coffeehouse&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The Coffehouse&lt;/a&gt;&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/wlZEam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&amp;quot;Discussing the War in a Paris Café&amp;quot;, The Illustrated London News 17 September 1870&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&quot;Discussing the War in a Paris Café&quot;, The Illustrated London News 17 September 1870&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="120" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T07:49:03.007" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="30" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T09:31:00.263" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;The roast&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;followed by more text to sate the character demon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T09:31:00.263" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="31" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T09:54:17.403" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Grinder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are all delicious coffee beans ;-)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="16" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T09:54:17.403" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="32" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-28T09:56:12.100" Score="4" ViewCount="42" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not talking about recipes for specific coffees, but more like recipes for other food and drinks that include coffee, perhaps even as the primary flavour.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, coffee desserts, coffee milkshakes, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should these be considered on topic here because they involve coffee to such an extent that the choice of bean / roast etc, is likely to affect overall flavour, or should they be designated as off-topic because they are not, in and of themselves, coffees.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To add to that, if we are to ban questions about coffee milkshakes, where do we draw the line between some of the milkier, flavoured iced coffees and milkshakes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T06:12:49.627" Title="Should questions about recipes involving coffee be considered off topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;topicality&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="33" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2015-01-28T10:01:41.423" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think it is a shame that sharing knowledge of good coffee types/roasts is likely to be off topic here but I think that the subjective nature and potential for spam is something that could degrade the quality of this site (in particular the latter). I don't know what the overseers think about this as it would be a shame to not capture and share recommendations with the rest of the community. In the early days of SO some of the most useful pages which are now off topic were good book recommendations and so forth which then became wikis. So is it possible that a wiki of recommended coffee beans/roasts is permissable, I don't know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The problem with chat rooms is I don't know how permanent the postings are and how searchable it is. It could still work though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T10:01:41.423" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="34" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T10:07:27.860" Score="-3" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;The Baristas&quot;, or even &quot;The Barista Room&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T10:07:27.860" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="35" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T10:40:08.020" Score="-2" Body="&lt;h2&gt;The Jampot&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jamaica_Wine_House&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;first coffee shop in London&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T10:40:08.020" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="36" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-28T10:47:22.410" Score="1" ViewCount="59" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/07/the-7-essential-meta-questions-of-every-beta/&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; it states:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Don’t ask about…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Questions that are primarily opinion-based&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/124/why-do-some-people-sneer-at-starbucks-coffee&quot;&gt;question&lt;/a&gt; I think is likely to elicit opinions and subjective answers and probably should be considered off topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do we think these types of questions should be considered on topic for this site?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="8" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T23:30:35.340" Title="Do we consider this question on topic" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="37" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2015-01-28T12:03:06.817" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;A coffee bean. This was basically the idea i had in mind when i made the proposal to begin with. Everything we talk about is based on the coffee bean.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="16" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T12:03:06.817" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="38" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2015-01-28T12:30:01.167" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think they're unavoidable for a topic such as this. Gear is, like it or not, an &lt;em&gt;essential&lt;/em&gt; part of making and enjoying great coffee and there's a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of it available. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Asking for an honest product recommendation doesn't make for a bad question; asking in a manner that invites dozens of answers due to a lack of scope and constraint makes for a bad question. There are only a limited number of double-walled glass presses in a 2 cup size, and I'd be quite put off if I came to a site all &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; coffee and couldn't ask which one was also likely to hold up in a dishwasher. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions that &lt;em&gt;don't&lt;/em&gt; limit the potential number of answers that could be received are by nature too broad, and you have a close reason for those available to you. I'd wait, see if these &lt;em&gt;actually become&lt;/em&gt; a problem, and enjoy giving thorough answers to the more interesting ones while you do. It's fine to have a zero-tolerance spam policy as many of our other sites have adopted, and an inclination to burn link-only or astroturf-like answers as you see them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But don't stop yourself from recommending a brand if you're happy with that brand. I love Breville's products and I recommended one of their grinders to someone earlier today, in the course of writing a thorough answer. And if spammers start writing comprehensive, thorough answers that receive up-votes then we can basically say &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://xkcd.com/810/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;mission accomplished&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.softwarerecs.stackexchange.com/questions/336/what-is-required-for-a-question-to-contain-enough-information&quot;&gt;Software Recommendations&lt;/a&gt; does a pretty good job of getting this right, and I'm sure that you could too. But, please, don't solve problems that you don't yet have - these types of questions are quite common in this topic, make &lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt; you're doing yourselves a favor before shutting them down and you &lt;em&gt;can't&lt;/em&gt; do that based on less than 100 questions so far in a private beta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T12:30:01.167" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="40" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T14:10:16.197" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;The Puck&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Was also thinking &quot;The Whack Box&quot;, but terminology might not be consistent there. I think 'puck' is universal for the spent grounds in a portafilter. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T14:10:16.197" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="41" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T14:43:28.223" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since we're throwing out ideas how about &quot;Crema&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="141" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-02-02T15:37:42.127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-02T15:37:42.127" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="42" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="12" CreationDate="2015-01-28T16:53:09.193" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;That's a good question. I, as a user of this site, would be interested in health questions but you made a good point - is the community able to appropriately answer the question? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good answers will have to link to their sources. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would vote that we should allow such questions but the community will have to be vigilant regarding duplicate questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="141" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T16:53:09.193" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="43" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-28T21:02:08.250" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;Nighthawks&quot;.   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Too subtle?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It is referring to the name of this quite famous painting of a café late at night:  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/efbFi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(From &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nighthawks&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T21:02:08.250" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="44" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="14" CreationDate="2015-01-28T22:31:59.327" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think all flavor questions should be fair game - there is an entire field (sensory science) dedicated to understanding human perception and preferences of flavor. Many of us are interested in coffee! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, I answered &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/96/how-will-cold-brewed-coffee-differ-from-traditional-hot-water-extration-method/194#194&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt;, using a system that robustly measures flavor, and without including biased opinions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="100" LastActivityDate="2015-01-28T22:31:59.327" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="46" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-29T01:29:39.570" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;Coffee Drops&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or a variation on the idea, such as &quot;Coffee Dripping&quot;, &quot;Coffee Brewing&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="98" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T01:29:39.570" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="47" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="12" CreationDate="2015-01-29T03:39:27.267" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Health advice should be left to a doctor. We can never know enough about a person to answer such a question on calcium deficiency. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand something like, which coffee will hurt my stomach less? May fall into our field. The line is blurred right now, and I can tell you the first question should not be answered by us, but this second one could be.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T03:39:27.267" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="48" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="49" CreationDate="2015-01-29T04:07:49.210" Score="11" ViewCount="73" Body="&lt;p&gt;With no intention of singling someone out, I am wondering if posts that include links that further self-interest are considered off topic. I am aware of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/5/should-product-recommendations-be-on-topic&quot;&gt;&quot;Should product recommendations be on-topic?&quot;&lt;/a&gt;, but I feel like this could be slightly different. Examples that I've seen:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/184/how-can-i-go-about-developing-my-ability-to-taste-flavors-in-coffee/198#198&quot;&gt;&quot;How can I go about developing my ability to taste flavors in coffee?&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/96/how-will-cold-brewed-coffee-differ-from-traditional-hot-water-extration-method/194#194&quot;&gt;How will “cold brewed” coffee differ from traditional hot-water extration methods?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/123/when-does-coffee-go-off/166#166&quot;&gt;When does coffee go off?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/66/what-coffees-are-the-least-acidic/181#181&quot;&gt;What coffees are the least acidic?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now these are just what has already developed on the website and the information that was provided was relevant, but was directing us to the product that created the data relevant? What if they were links to beans I roasted, brewing products I've created, or a cafe that I own? If a top post, is a link to a Chemex that I can purchase through a &lt;em&gt;Peet's Coffee&lt;/em&gt;, wouldn't the forum function as an unpaid advertisement? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a note, I feel that those were all well structured answers and great contributions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastEditorUserId="17" LastEditDate="2015-01-29T04:34:45.490" LastActivityDate="2015-02-02T02:15:01.410" Title="Do we allow self-endorsements here?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="49" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="48" CreationDate="2015-01-29T04:51:57.547" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;If they're well structured answers that were supported by a link given to something the author is affiliated with, it's generally fine. This is what to look for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; of their answers in some way promote their product? That &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; be a red flag, not &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt;, but can be. Some people just come to sites specifically to answer questions about their product. Look carefully.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are many of their answers that also mention their product only &lt;em&gt;tangentially&lt;/em&gt; related to the question at hand? That can spell trouble, if someone is looking for places to plant stuff&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do they clearly mention that it's their link? That's important, as it asserts a sort of &quot;I hereby assert that this is given in good faith in the spirit of being helpful&quot; thing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We positively &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; people whose job is coffee on this site, those are your professionals, the people that do lots of science and can answer tougher questions, especially about the brewing process. If they support some of their answers with stuff they're affiliated with, that's great. If they go a bit too overboard, moderators have means of contacting them to let them know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;With that said...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Coffee is a topic that is &lt;em&gt;ripe&lt;/em&gt; with products (no pun intended), and we will see our fair share of folks that have come here for the wrong reasons. Fortunately, most of us have a very good ability to determine when something just &lt;em&gt;doesn't seem right&lt;/em&gt; - and we give you the ability to flag things for moderator attention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you see something that gives you a bit of pause, and you &lt;em&gt;seriously&lt;/em&gt; wonder if the person is here for the wrong reasons, flag it as 'other' and let us / the moderators-to-be have a look at it. &lt;em&gt;Blatant&lt;/em&gt; spam obviously deserves a spam flag directly, I'm talking about the &quot;If it weren't for the other answers in their history linking to the same site, this would seem completely benign&quot; sorts of things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our job as hosts is to make people feel welcome and do our best to basically get out of their way as they participate. The fewer rules, the better. If this becomes a major problem down the road we can revisit it, but for now, I think it's sufficient if folks just keep an eye out for anything (or, to the point, anyone) going sideways with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T04:51:57.547" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="50" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="32" CreationDate="2015-01-29T06:12:49.627" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's pretty simple. If they're asking about brewing components, or brewing technique - they're on topic. If it's more about cooking components, or cooking technique, then it's probably one for &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Seasoned Advice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is going to be overlap, and you should be &lt;em&gt;insanely&lt;/em&gt; jealous when it comes to your site - you want any good question that fits within the topic to stay &lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;. Coffee is a common ingredient in many popular deserts, and fits well here, as long as the 'gist' requires knowledge of not just cooking, but also coffee in order to answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wouldn't do anything now, there's less than 200 questions so far, and the site isn't even public yet. When you get to ~500 questions and there's a bigger sampling of these, then it's &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; easier to identify factors that make something a solid fit here rather than somewhere else. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T06:12:49.627" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="51" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="12" CreationDate="2015-01-29T14:56:12.690" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think personal health advice should be off-topic, but requests for references to research on the physiology and genetics of caffeine response should be on-topic.  See for example &lt;a href=&quot;http://genes.uchicago.edu/wp-content/uploads/palmer/Yang%20A%20et%20al%20Psychopharm%202010.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this &quot;twin&quot; study on caffeine intolerance and genetics&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That raises the question of how &quot;good&quot; (authoritative) sources should be.  I doubt there is a bright line test that can be applied, as for example the question yesterday about &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/139/is-kopi-luwak-safe-to-drink&quot;&gt;safety of drinking Kopi Luwak coffee&lt;/a&gt;.  It can be, as far as I'm concerned, left to the voting up/down of Answers to police the use of reliable sources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="34" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T14:56:12.690" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="52" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="79" CreationDate="2015-01-29T17:05:34.633" Score="8" ViewCount="106" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some things are experienced first-hand but does it imply that the person is factually correct all the time? There might just be people asking serious health-related issues and we might tell them about our opinion  (which is wrong) but it can either be correct and not work because of natural causes or it might be blatant lies. So, should we source every answer we put, or atleast suggest verification sources?&#xA;For more info on what is &lt;strong&gt;original research&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:No_original_research&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:No_original_research&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT:&lt;/strong&gt; I would appreciate more community input. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="132" LastEditorUserId="132" LastEditDate="2015-02-05T14:41:37.097" LastActivityDate="2015-02-11T20:51:16.203" Title="Should original research be allowed?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="53" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2015-01-29T17:29:36.437" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Unless the question calls for opinion (which, in general, they shouldn't), everything should be backed with published, verifiable evidence, IMO. Anecdotes are &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; evidence and so should be avoided. Even though coffee is a highly subjective experience, there is quite a bit of research on the topic and we should utilize that when answering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the term &quot;Original Research&quot; is a tiny bit misleading to someone who doesn't read that link because all answers require research. I know it means no &quot;unattributable&quot; text, and I think we should include something to that effect, I just don't know if &quot;Original Research&quot; is the best way to convey that, someone might get scared away from answering because they think they're unable to write an answer in their own words (which is fine, as long the answer contains attributable facts).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I go to SE for high-quality answers to high-quality questions and compromising on that doesn't seem like a good direction to go for this site. We don't want to go the way of yahoo answers...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="78" LastEditorUserId="78" LastEditDate="2015-02-02T17:51:40.760" LastActivityDate="2015-02-02T17:51:40.760" CommentCount="9" />
  <row Id="54" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2015-01-29T20:36:35.037" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;Wikipedia's policy is tilted toward the use of &lt;em&gt;secondary sources&lt;/em&gt;, almost to the exclusion of primary sources, with the intention of providing conclusions that have a consensus status.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't think that should be our approach.  I may be coming from a mix of StackExchange sites where it is often possible for somewhat naive questions to get responses from bona fide experts.  In any case I see value in the experience of community members informing answers, and generally the community voting can be relied upon to catch out speculation and self-promotion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="34" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T20:36:35.037" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="55" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2015-01-29T20:48:55.387" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;We have a New Questions feed on another site that I frequent. It's a great way to make sure frequent chat users are reviewing all incoming questions. Being a brand new beta, it would also be a good place for some of the discussions that will happen around what is on/off topic. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/feeds&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="104" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T20:48:55.387" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="56" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-01-29T22:28:17.143" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bean Me Up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This appeals to my sci-fi nerdy background!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do know that it is an existing &lt;a href=&quot;http://beanmeup.com.au/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Coffee Shop&lt;/a&gt;, but if there are no copyright issues, it would be awesome!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="179" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T22:28:17.143" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="57" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-01-29T22:56:05.127" Score="2" ViewCount="28" Body="&lt;p&gt;On mobile (specifically android 4, chrome)  on both coffee and meta.coffee has an issue with the bar that has Questions, Tags, Users, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The hightlighted option has a red underline, but the text almost disappears - it is very very close to the backgroud color and invisible unless fully zoomed in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="175" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T22:56:05.127" Title="Theme issue on mobile" Tags="&lt;bug&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="58" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="36" CreationDate="2015-01-29T23:30:35.340" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;There has to be &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; leeway sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;SFF-Stack&lt;/a&gt; there is an &quot;Off-Topic&quot; close reason of:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Questions seeking &lt;strong&gt;scientific solutions or explanations&lt;/strong&gt; are off-topic unless they relate directly to a cited work of fiction. There are a number of other Stack Exchange sites dedicated to answering questions on non-fictional sciences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/s9KU4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Scientific-Off-Topic.JPG&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But there are several questions which ask for purely 'scientific explanations' which have been left open (after much discussion). Some of them are even considered to be the site's most popular questions. Examples:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/questions/43651/is-sheldon-right-that-superman-would-have-killed-lois-when-he-caught-her&quot;&gt;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/questions/43651/is-sheldon-right-that-superman-would-have-killed-lois-when-he-caught-her&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/questions/28862/how-did-the-cookfire-get-hot-enough-to-melt-gold-in-game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/questions/28862/how-did-the-cookfire-get-hot-enough-to-melt-gold-in-game-of-thrones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/questions/72925/why-is-there-no-electricity-available-in-the-walking-dead-series&quot;&gt;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/questions/72925/why-is-there-no-electricity-available-in-the-walking-dead-series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As long as we define what we can allow, and what we can't.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suggest that we let the question sit for a little while, see what types of answers pop-up. If the answers are low quality / primarily opinion-based, then we can surmise that the question is not a good fit for this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="179" LastActivityDate="2015-01-29T23:30:35.340" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="59" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="48" CreationDate="2015-02-01T18:38:41.347" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;The posts in question are all my own - Hi everyone! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm here because I'm a coffee and tasting professional, and I want to help guide people though experiencing flavors, brewing better coffee, and understanding all the things that go into making coffee interesting, unique, and great. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I feel I can answer many of these questions better than nearly any other individual or organization because I work for a company that has around ~20,000+ coffee reviews on a full sensory system. &lt;strong&gt;I am allowed to use and post graphs and information derived from that data as long as I include a link back to the company.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the exception of &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/184/how-can-i-go-about-developing-my-ability-to-taste-flavors-in-coffee/198#198&quot;&gt;How can I go about developing my ability to taste flavors in coffee?&lt;/a&gt;&quot; all of my answers are highly up-voted answers; that question obviously crossed the line with the community into pure 'promotion' (despite the votes, I believe the app helps individuals learn to taste - but I did a poor job of communicating it). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I hope to continue to answer questions and support this community while staying on the right side of the self promotion line&lt;/strong&gt;. If/when I fail at that, please let me know - my email is in my profile. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="100" LastEditorUserId="100" LastEditDate="2015-02-02T02:15:01.410" LastActivityDate="2015-02-02T02:15:01.410" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="60" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="74" CreationDate="2015-02-02T09:29:18.040" Score="4" ViewCount="52" Body="&lt;p&gt;Current we have &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/stovetop&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'stovetop'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;stovetop&lt;/a&gt; (1), &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/percolator&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'percolator'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;percolator&lt;/a&gt; (1), and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/moka&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'moka'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;moka&lt;/a&gt; (2). These are all different words for the same thing, and we should unify them into a single tag. So:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;What tag do we pick for this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once we've decided, can synonyms be created from the other two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastEditorUserId="127" LastEditDate="2015-02-10T15:17:05.807" LastActivityDate="2015-02-10T15:17:05.807" Title="Tag Synonym Request: stovetop, percolator -&gt; moka" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tagging&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="61" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="60" CreationDate="2015-02-02T09:32:02.667" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would suggest we use &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/moka&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'moka'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;moka&lt;/a&gt; as the tag. Not only is it what the people who invented it call it, but it's the most popular term according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.co.uk/trends/explore#q=moka%2C%20percolator%2C%20stovetop&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Google Trends&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/1Pr9j.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastEditorUserId="127" LastEditDate="2015-02-02T11:12:05.817" LastActivityDate="2015-02-02T11:12:05.817" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="62" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-02T14:04:36.153" Score="2" ViewCount="77" Body="&lt;p&gt;A lot of stack exchange sites require that the asker demonstrates that they have made some prior effort to solve the problem themselves before asking the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should we do the same?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If so, what level of effort should we require, and what sort of proof should we accept that this effort has been expended?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T01:20:36.107" Title="Should we require proof of prior effort?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;asking-questions&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="63" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="62" CreationDate="2015-02-02T15:35:57.260" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;No. If a question is clear and answerable, it should be answered. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not all questions &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; a historical context or a show of prior efforts. If a bit of background context makes a question clearer, the author should provide it. But when a community makes that a site-wide &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;requirement&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, too often it becomes overdone when communities feels &lt;em&gt;compelled&lt;/em&gt; to enforce these rules everywhere, regardless of merit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a question can be made clearer by providing more context, you can easily ask the author for clarification in a comment. With a bit of thoughtful guidance, you create a pleasant end-user experience for all. But when every other question is rubber stamped with &lt;em&gt;&quot;What have you tried?&quot;,&lt;/em&gt; it can start to look a bit forced and unnecessary, and even a bit harassing. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-02-02T19:25:35.197" LastActivityDate="2015-02-02T19:25:35.197" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="64" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-02-03T09:54:26.290" Score="-1" Body="&lt;h1&gt;Java&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-03T09:54:26.290" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="65" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-05T03:20:47.353" Score="1" ViewCount="24" Body="&lt;p&gt;We have two mainsite tags thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/q/139/47&quot;&gt;this question on kopi luwak&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/kopiluwak&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'kopiluwak'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;kopiluwak&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/weaselcoffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'weaselcoffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;weaselcoffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tag convention is to hyphenate spaces in a name, not skip them, so these tags should be: &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/kopi-luwak&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'kopi-luwak'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;kopi-luwak&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/weasel-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'weasel-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;weasel-coffee&lt;/a&gt;. The latter should probably be a synonym, since we don't need two tags for the same coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Could a moderator replace these tags?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="47" LastActivityDate="2015-02-05T08:43:32.370" Title="Rename [kopiluwak] and [weaselcoffee] to hyphenate their names" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="66" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="65" CreationDate="2015-02-05T08:43:32.370" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Just checking, we're keeping &lt;em&gt;luwak&lt;/em&gt; and not &lt;em&gt;alamid&lt;/em&gt; (as it's known in most of the rest of SE Asia?) I'm fine with that, as luwak is how it's been made famous, I just want to make sure before I go doing tag surgery :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-02-05T08:43:32.370" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="67" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2015-02-06T14:14:32.833" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/feeds/tag?tagnames=coffee&amp;amp;sort=newest&quot;&gt;Newest [coffee] questions on Seasoned Advice&lt;/a&gt;. Might be some good overlap if people putting coffee in ovens (or whatever it is they do over there) need advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-06T14:14:32.833" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="68" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="72" CreationDate="2015-02-08T20:35:30.607" Score="2" ViewCount="22" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is currently one question tagged with &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavour&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavour'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavour&lt;/a&gt;, and several others taged with &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavor&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavor'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavor&lt;/a&gt;. There is also a tag &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/coffee-taste&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'coffee-taste'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;coffee-taste&lt;/a&gt;. Since I doubt anyone has enough rep to create a synonym yet, I made this meta post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These could potentially all be merged.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What should be used? Can a SE person please unify the questions / make synonyms? Are there any other variations of this already in use that should also be merged?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-02-09T16:01:45.063" LastActivityDate="2015-02-09T16:50:03.697" Title="Potential tag synonyms: flavor, flavour, coffee-taste" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;status-completed&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="69" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="62" CreationDate="2015-02-08T20:37:29.023" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's generally pretty obvious when a question would have been trivial to research beforehand (or could be improved if the author had researched it a bit before hand). At least at first, we should play it by ear and let the community decide on a question by question basis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hard rules about things that are potentially subjective are a bad idea IMO. If the question is a good fit, and clearly defined, it's probably okay (even if it could have been solved by a quick search).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-02-08T20:37:29.023" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="72" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="68" CreationDate="2015-02-09T16:01:19.293" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I merged the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavor&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavor'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavor&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/taste&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'taste'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;taste&lt;/a&gt; tags and and created a synonym mapping from &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/taste&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'taste'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;taste&lt;/a&gt; → &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavor&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavor'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to regional spelling variations, we've standardized on the US variant. There's no need to create a synonym for &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavour&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavour'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavour&lt;/a&gt; because the text completion will suggest the correct tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-02-09T16:50:03.697" LastActivityDate="2015-02-09T16:50:03.697" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="73" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2015-02-09T23:08:30.040" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Product recommendations should be on-topic if they are answer to a specific question.  Product recommendations are not on topic when they are the answer to a non-specific or primarily opinion based question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;What home roaster takes up the least space, uses the least electricity and produces the least amount of smoke?&quot;  - On-Topic Product Recommendation.  Products that do not answer the question are easy flagged as spam or downvoted as bad answers.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;What shop in Portlandia makes the best espresso?&quot; - Off-topic Product Recommendation.  The answers are inherently opinion based because the question itself is bad and can't be salvaged.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="76" LastActivityDate="2015-02-09T23:08:30.040" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="74" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="60" CreationDate="2015-02-10T12:53:42.783" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I call moka and percolator very different things; I think [moka] and [percolator] should remain separate and distinct.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moka_pot&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Moka&lt;/a&gt; is what some call a stovetop espresso maker, which I think is a misnomer anyway.  But it uses pressure to force water through grounds.  Water goes through the grounds (which are in the middle of the device) once into a storage vessel on top, which is separate from the chamber in which the water was added at the beginning of the brew.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I call &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coffee_percolator&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;percolator&lt;/a&gt; something that boils water and drips it over grounds repeatedly.  There is no separate storage vessel for the coffee once brewed; water (at first) or (partially-brewed) coffee is repeatedly boiled and dripped over the grounds (which are instead at the top of the chamber).  The brewed coffee ends up where the plain water was at the beginning of the brew.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have both devices, and use them differently; e.g., a coarser grind for percolator.  I find the outcome of percolated coffee to be more like French press or perhaps drip; moka is more like Turkish coffee or espresso. Though similar in concept, they're (to me) totally different in outcome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is this a regional terminology difference?  Am I splitting hairs, or have I been doing this wrong all the years?? :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I agree to drop &quot;stovetop&quot; as it's ambiguous.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-02-10T12:53:42.783" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="75" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="84" CreationDate="2015-02-10T17:00:34.253" Score="6" ViewCount="44" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am apparently not the only one who's ever been confused about this.  Meta sites &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/87890/262760&quot;&gt;do not have an edit queue&lt;/a&gt;, and so the &quot;edit&quot; link is not active for (other users') questions and answers on [meta] for those with less than some threshold rep (1k or 2k depending on the site).  The only reason seems to be &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/a/97371/262760&quot;&gt;that it isn't necessary&lt;/a&gt; and/or it's harmful to add another queue for mods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The help section says that &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help/editing&quot;&gt;any user should be able to suggest edits&lt;/a&gt;, which is true on the [main] site.  But because there's no suggested-edit queue it seems that the edit ability on [meta] only for higher-rep users (1000+; 2000+ on &quot;mature&quot; sites), which is the trusted-user rep threshold at which point you can make edits directly (without going into a suggestion-queue). I suppose this means that at 1k rep you can also edit meta directly, but it's a little awkward to suggest stuff that ought to be changed &quot;out of band&quot;.  This discourages editing on [meta], which may be a fine thing, but I think it also reduces &lt;em&gt;participation&lt;/em&gt;, which is probably not a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's an apparently-stalled (years-old) &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/129033/262760&quot;&gt;feature request&lt;/a&gt; to expand edit features in [meta]s. Does anyone else want this?  Mods / high-rep users, do you &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; want this? Is this reasonable for beta-sites, like this one (as of this writing)? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suspect this too much of an uphill battle, with losing cost-benefit, of marginal value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastEditorUserId="101" LastEditDate="2015-02-12T16:19:44.487" LastActivityDate="2015-02-12T16:19:44.487" Title="Can we turn on suggest-edit for this meta?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;feature-request&gt;&lt;status-declined&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="76" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="75" CreationDate="2015-02-11T02:00:26.160" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want this quite a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over on &lt;a href=&quot;http://rpg.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;RPG.SE&lt;/a&gt; I'm a prolific editor. On other sites I visit I also propose a lot of edits. My &lt;em&gt;main mode&lt;/em&gt; of interaction with Stack Exchange sites at this point is to edit and improve content already there. I've proposed some edits on here, too. (My accepted:rejected ratio is pretty high in favour of accepted edits at this point.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But on Meta, I hover over that greyed-out &lt;em&gt;edit&lt;/em&gt; link on a post a couple of days old to make an improvement that stands out, and I click it, and then I sigh quietly and move on to continue reading.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If there were a feature that let me actually suggest edits here on meta I'd like that, and I'd use it a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="47" LastActivityDate="2015-02-11T02:00:26.160" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="77" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="78" CreationDate="2015-02-11T16:16:37.473" Score="2" ViewCount="29" Body="&lt;p&gt;I see two tags that seem to be synonymous:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/drip&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'drip'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;drip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/drip-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'drip-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;drip-coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can't think of any use of &quot;drip&quot; that's on-topic here that would not be identical to &quot;drip-coffee&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edits: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As @Robert says below, the right way is merge/rename/delete to have only one tag.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;removed this ill considered aside... &lt;strike&gt;Meta-meta: should &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; tag on Coffee.SE contain the string &quot;coffee&quot;?&lt;/strike&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastEditorUserId="262" LastEditDate="2015-02-12T14:37:17.447" LastActivityDate="2015-02-12T14:37:17.447" Title="Retag-request: merge drip and drip-coffee (completed)" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;status-completed&gt;&lt;retag-request&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="78" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="77" CreationDate="2015-02-11T20:04:46.597" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;The process is actually called &quot;drip brewing&quot;, so I would just rename the tag(s) to &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/drip-brew&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'drip-brew'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;drip-brew&lt;/a&gt;. No synonym needed; text completion will help users find the proper tag: &lt;kbd&gt;d&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;r&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;i&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;p&lt;/kbd&gt; &amp;rarr; &lt;kbd&gt;drip-brew&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meta-meta answer: I didn't actually have a problem with using the word &quot;coffee&quot; in a tag&amp;hellip; assuming that was the proper nomenclature for that particular process. Calling it something else would not help improve clarity, but we don't have a tag called &quot;french press coffee&quot; or &quot;moka coffee&quot;, so in this case, the point is somewhat moot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" LastActivityDate="2015-02-11T20:04:46.597" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="79" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2015-02-11T20:51:16.203" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I maintain that original research should be permitted; coffee is a mix of science and art:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;substantiating references should be provided (and expected) for factually verifiable data: e.g., scientific facts; and&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&quot;original research&quot; or experiential recounting should be permissible for the &quot;artful&quot; aspects of coffee; e.g., techniques.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hopefully expanding on @hardmath's answer, I believe that community input and verification is the mechanism to ensure a high quality of information, no matter what its source. &lt;strong&gt;I think there are three issues here: fact, art, and opinion.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If something is a verifiable &lt;strong&gt;fact&lt;/strong&gt;: e.g., &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kirk never said &quot;Beam me up, Scotty!&quot; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beam_me_up,_Scotty&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;refs from here&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Han Solo &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/character/ch0000002/quotes&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;did say&lt;/a&gt; &quot;I'm in it for the money.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These facts &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; be (and indeed &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be) backed up by a reference. If they're not there, they can be (and should be) added. If they're false, a countering reference can be provided, and/or the statement gets downvoted, deleted, edited, etc. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Art-, experience-, or technique-based&lt;/strong&gt; questions and answers are legitimate; for example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;speculation, such as about &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/q/383/262&quot;&gt;diner coffee taste&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;actual literal art or technique &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/q/345/262&quot;&gt;of latte foam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;experiential or traditional factors in serving and drinking coffee, like &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/q/157/262&quot;&gt;wide serving cups&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These happen to also be high-rating (10+ as of this writing), popular questions; but that doesn't itself make them legitimate. In some cases, these can (and should) be backed up with citations or references.  Are those examples of non-fact, and are they legitimate?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Purely &lt;strong&gt;opinion-based&lt;/strong&gt; questions and answers &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/a/201995/262760&quot;&gt;are generally not welcome&lt;/a&gt;, and I don't think this site should be any different.  Except, of course, in meta sites, where (paradoxically?) opinion is largely the &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; topic being discussed. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-02-11T20:51:16.203" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="80" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-11T21:25:24.493" Score="4" ViewCount="50" Body="&lt;p&gt;This was inspired by a few recent posts. Currently we have a couple of tags: &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ground-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'ground-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ground-coffee&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavored-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavored-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavored-coffee&lt;/a&gt; that contain the word. While the second could lose it easily enough (maybe &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavorings&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavorings'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavorings&lt;/a&gt; would be nicer?), what about the first? &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ground&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'ground'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ground&lt;/a&gt; doesn't feel quite right, but neither does having 'coffee' in the tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So this question is two fold:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should the word coffee be removed/banned from all tag names?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If so, what do we do with the existing ones that do have it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-25T01:02:52.283" Title="Can tags contain the word 'coffee'?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="81" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="80" CreationDate="2015-02-11T22:47:14.620" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't think &quot;coffee&quot; needs to be banned outright from tags, though if others disagree I won't hold that position at all strongly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; want to remove it from tags, I might suggest replacing the existing ones with &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/grinding&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'grinding'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;grinding&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavoring&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavoring'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavoring&lt;/a&gt;. They're a little less odd than just &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ground&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'ground'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ground&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavor&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavor'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavor&lt;/a&gt;, especially because &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavor&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavor'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavor&lt;/a&gt; is more likely to describe questions about how different types and styles of bean, grind, or preparation can affect flavor--which is a different topic entirely from discussing flavored coffee. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="37" LastActivityDate="2015-02-11T22:47:14.620" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="82" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2015-02-11T23:36:17.020" Score="0" Body="&lt;h1&gt;Moka Mocha&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They rhyme and it sounds awesome and rolls off the tongue. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-11T23:36:17.020" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="83" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="80" CreationDate="2015-02-12T00:22:55.683" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Personally I don't think that coffee should be removed from the tags unless it is very redundant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, the tag  &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavored-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavored-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavored-coffee&lt;/a&gt; would be much more ambiguous as &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavoring&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavoring'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavoring&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavor&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavor'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavor&lt;/a&gt;. You could then be talking about the flavor of the coffee, or adding flavor shots to a coffee. I think that in certain tags, especially ones like &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavored-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavored-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavored-coffee&lt;/a&gt;, we need to keep the word &lt;strong&gt;coffee&lt;/strong&gt;. I feel like &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ground-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'ground-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ground-coffee&lt;/a&gt; needs to have the word coffee in it too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other situations, such as &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/dark-roast-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'dark-roast-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;dark-roast-coffee&lt;/a&gt;, I think that it could be removed entirely. That example is just a hypothetical one though to show where it does get redundant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="225" LastActivityDate="2015-02-12T00:22:55.683" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="84" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="75" CreationDate="2015-02-12T16:19:33.577" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;A compelling reason for doing this is giving people the ability to do other people favors in a very neatly-packaged way, something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I understand what you're saying, but your last two sentences lost me. I suggested an edit that might clarify what you're trying to express without changing the intent of your post&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The person can then just review the edit, and apply it or change it slightly if they agree. On meta, where it's &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; more about voice, that's pretty ideal. Unfortunately the way you've proposed it is just not technically feasible. I'll go into why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;The voices, man, I keep hearing 'em!&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every suggested edit generates an inbox notification. On sites like Ask Ubuntu, Ask Different, Stack Overflow and others where meta sees significantly more participation than other sites, this would create &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt; of noise. The alternative is not generating inbox notifications for child meta suggested edits, which (unfortunately, for the most part) means they'd go unseen or approved in a queue by others, and &lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt; not be something the author would have approved as suggested. Meta is a town hall; that's why you need privileges to edit directly on the main site to edit here, one of the chief reasons anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Killed by slow, and do you even meta?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On sites that &lt;em&gt;don't&lt;/em&gt; have very active child meta sites, participation is &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; lower. Turning on work queues here would just mean creating a backlog that moderators would feel obliged to clean out from time to time. It just wouldn't work as you intend it to work. Showing them in the &lt;em&gt;main&lt;/em&gt; site queue alleviates that to some extent, but that's shown to everyone regardless of meta participation. Queues where you accomplish small units of work are already a big ask on the main site, I really don't want to mix them. As meta sites tend to take on their own culture over time, I don't want non-participants here reviewing suggested edits because the system asked them to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;I am a mean, horrible person.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But with all of that said, turning our engine sort of upside down for discussion here on meta worked well enough. But, it's missing stuff. There aren't any polls, people can get down-voted for asking for support, curating is sort of second class and opportunistic and using it as a bug tracker could be made much more ideal. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;hope&lt;/em&gt; to take on a project this year that takes a serious look at child meta sites, and how they could perhaps diverge a bit in terms of features from the main sites. This is something I'd like to see possible, just ... better, not bolted on. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm declining it as proposed, but that doesn't make it a bad idea. In fact it's a good one (heck, I up-voted it), but in need of some groundwork that I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; want to do.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-02-12T16:19:33.577" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="85" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="62" CreationDate="2015-02-13T01:20:36.107" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;It will depend. You can say &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;NO&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; when the answer seems to be clear and thoughtful. In the answer, the reader should be able to assume (and maybe see) that:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was research done/knowledge is acceptable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information is clear and useful&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's long enough to provide sufficient information to answer the questions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not a copy-paste answer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can request the proof of prior research (that means &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;YES&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;) if the reader assumes/sees that:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is not a lot of information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a couple sentences long (unless that is sufficient)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information is debateable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looks like its an exact replica of a section in a website&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This should be the key points for readers to look for when searching &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;valid and proved&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; answers. I hope this answers you question!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T01:20:36.107" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="86" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-13T01:39:42.933" Score="3" ViewCount="69" Body="&lt;p&gt;Here at Coffee Stack Exchange, we reached public beta about three days ago! This is exciting as we're slowly moving towards being a non-beta site! Graduated Stack Exchange sites have their own themes, including different icons for stuff like badges. Let's start thinking about what we'd like our site to look like: please answer this question with ideas about stuff like badge icons, downvote/upvote buttons, color themes, even the background! All ideas are appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="127" LastEditDate="2015-02-13T09:56:40.507" LastActivityDate="2015-03-15T23:46:19.173" Title="What should the design for our site look like?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="87" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="86" CreationDate="2015-02-13T01:48:24.803" Score="1" Body="&lt;h1&gt;Badge Icons&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My recommendation is that instead of the plain colored circles, there should be coffee cups. This would work great since who doesn't want a cup of coffee? This is like awarding cups of coffee to people. :-)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Downvote and Upvote Buttons&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would like to keep them just the way they are for some SE originality and it is easier to know what you are doing. If comfortable enough, there might be a green thumbs up for the upvote button and a red thumbs down for the downvote button.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Word Color&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would like to be optional will variety of colors. I'm think of chocolate brown, black, brown, light brown, and all sorts of brown and coffee related colors!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Background&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just like Area 51's alien themed background, I hope we have a coffee themed background. There would be coffee cups, coffee machines, coffee beans, steam, and a light brown paint underneath all the decorations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;Other&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well I got nothing else. I hope this gets chosen for the new Coffee SE site stlye (if this question survives and there are multiple answers...)! Good Luck to future answers and consider the other &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/28/what-logo-we-can-have-lets-start-working?lq=1&quot;&gt;meta question&lt;/a&gt; about the logo!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="75" LastEditDate="2015-02-13T23:05:41.527" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T23:05:41.527" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="88" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="80" CreationDate="2015-02-13T12:47:29.603" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;In general, if it would be obvious from the context that a tag refers to coffee (this is a coffee Q&amp;amp;A site, after all), we might as well leave it out. However, I don't see the need for a hard-and-fast rule here (or indeed, in most places on StackExchange sites).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As others have mentioned, other tags may &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; the word coffee in them for clarification (eg. &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavored-coffee&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavored-coffee'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavored-coffee&lt;/a&gt;, which is not the same thing as &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavor&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavor'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavor&lt;/a&gt;, or even &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/flavoring&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'flavoring'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;flavoring&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T12:47:29.603" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="89" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="12" CreationDate="2015-02-13T12:52:13.503" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;An excellent question; I don't see any reason to make health related questions off-topic, but I do suggest we make it clear that people should stick to actual verifiable research (lest we become bombarded with questions about ridiculous psudo-scientific claims).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm having a hard time describing the sort of thing I mean without potentially insulting someone, but you probably know the type and can imagine why that would possibly be bad for the sites image.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T12:52:13.503" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="90" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="92" CreationDate="2015-02-13T15:25:38.630" Score="3" ViewCount="273" Body="&lt;p&gt;When we talk about the substance left over after the brewing process, should we refer to it as coffee grinds or coffee grounds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am unsure which to use or which is the correct terminology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If they are both correct, should we choose one?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="225" LastActivityDate="2015-02-16T09:31:10.970" Title="Coffee terminology: Which is correct? Coffee grinds or grounds?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;terminology&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="91" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-13T15:33:58.013" Score="-3" ViewCount="51" Body="&lt;p&gt;Apparently &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/notesandqueries/query/0,5753,-25502,00.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;tea contains more caffeine than coffee&lt;/a&gt;. Does it mean tea questions can be on topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="294" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T15:37:03.327" Title="Are tea-related questions on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="92" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="90" CreationDate="2015-02-13T15:35:52.080" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: I am British&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here's how I see it: You grind beans. While you grind the beans, you can adjust the grind. That is to say &lt;strong&gt;the grind&lt;/strong&gt; is the process of grinding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The grounds are what you get after grinding. I would never call the product of grinding grinds, but then again see disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;grind&lt;/strong&gt; - (v.) To smash up beans. Past-tense: ground.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;grind&lt;/strong&gt; - (n.) The process of grinding. Adjusting how one grinds can be expressed as &quot;[modifying] the grind&quot;. Also can refer to the coarsness as appropriate for a certain method of extraction, e.g. &quot;an Espresso grind&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;grounds&lt;/strong&gt; - (n.) The result of grinding. Ground coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T15:35:52.080" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="93" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="91" CreationDate="2015-02-13T15:37:03.327" Score="8" Body="&lt;h1&gt;No&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But there's an &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/72875/tea&quot;&gt;Area 51 Proposal for tea&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T15:37:03.327" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="94" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2015-02-13T21:57:47.827" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;A cup of coffee with answers and questions coming out of the top of the cup like steam. I think it is very coffee related and original!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-13T21:57:47.827" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="95" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-14T10:56:00.927" Score="4" ViewCount="29" Body="&lt;p&gt;Are question about uses of pure coffee oil on topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The essential oil is processed through the process of cold pressing using the beans and is a dark brown colour in appearance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="294" LastActivityDate="2015-02-14T17:33:05.050" Title="Are questions about Coffee Bean Oil on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="96" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="95" CreationDate="2015-02-14T17:33:05.050" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;The beta at Area 51 is defined as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Beta Q&amp;amp;A site for people interested in all aspects of producing and consuming coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seems that pure coffee oil would fit that bill. I have no experience with coffee oil and I am guessing that is true of many other people, so a few well structured question and answers would be informative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="23" LastActivityDate="2015-02-14T17:33:05.050" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="97" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-15T06:31:04.860" Score="8" ViewCount="136" Body="&lt;p&gt;Fully launched StackExchange sites can show community ads for anything their community chooses. There are premade templates for ads for Area51 proposals:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/ads/proposal/61013.png&quot; alt=&quot;area51 ad&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but they're perhaps not the best for betas, since they still say &quot;proposal&quot; and are pretty generic. Is the premade one good enough? Or does anyone have something they'd like to offer up as an ad for any sites interested in advertising for coffee?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/a/247044/133299&quot;&gt;text on a simple image&lt;/a&gt; can look good. Here's one from space:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/qIjvZ.png&quot; alt=&quot;space community ad&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the image requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;The image that you create must be &lt;strong&gt;220 x 250 pixels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Must be hosted through our standard image uploader (imgur)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Must be GIF or PNG&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;No animated GIFs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Absolute limit on file size of 150 KB&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="230" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T20:22:50.053" Title="What should a community ad for coffee.stackexchange look like?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="98" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-16T00:00:31.590" Score="1" ViewCount="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;What should we list on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/about&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;About&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; page under &quot;ask about&quot; and &quot;don't ask about&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, what else should go on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help/on-topic&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;What topics can I ask about here?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help/dont-ask&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;What types of questions should I avoid asking?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; pages?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The initial work on this is essentially already done for us in the Area 51 proposal, but we'll want to flush these out further as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-02-16T00:00:31.590" Title="What should our documentation contain?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="99" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="90" CreationDate="2015-02-16T09:31:10.970" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've seen people refer to &lt;em&gt;grinds&lt;/em&gt; as what comes out of the grinder, and &lt;em&gt;grounds&lt;/em&gt; as the spent grinds you're left with after brewing. This isn't correct, and should be corrected, just make sure you look out for cases where the person &lt;em&gt;meant&lt;/em&gt; to imply &lt;strong&gt;spent grounds&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;fresh grounds&lt;/strong&gt; respectively. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-02-16T09:31:10.970" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="100" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="97" CreationDate="2015-02-16T11:09:31.843" Score="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.gaming.stackexchange.com/questions/10168/community-promotion-ads-2015&quot;&gt;Yes, this size will work fine&lt;/a&gt;, and it'll look nicer on high-dpi screens.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/LzvlP.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-16T11:09:31.843" CommentCount="14" />
  <row Id="101" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2015-02-16T13:56:00.227" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;For the sake of discussion, how about a variation on the icon from Ron Cobb?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The icon I refer to can be seen in... Alien from Ridley Scott. Cobb designed the &quot;Semiotic Standard For All Commercial Trans-Stellar Utility Lifter And Heavy Element Transport Spacecraft&quot;. One of the icons is a simple, straight coffee cup. You can see it on a &lt;a href=&quot;http://design.iconfactory.com/ios-7-and-alien/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;reproduction by a software company&lt;/a&gt; (see around the middle of the page).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea here is that this is very nerdy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On a side note, an icon like that one could be for the chat room.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="98" LastActivityDate="2015-02-16T13:56:00.227" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="102" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="104" CreationDate="2015-02-16T16:38:17.187" Score="0" ViewCount="33" Body="&lt;p&gt;Does it make sense to ask a question with not one specific answer, but many different answers to collect a list of things like &quot;known coffee types&quot; together with preparation method or is this more a wiki thing to collect them?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="302" LastEditorUserId="302" LastEditDate="2015-02-16T16:53:48.247" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T01:12:12.230" Title="Is &quot;What type of coffee do you know?&quot;, a valid question?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="103" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-16T21:51:04.520" Score="10" ViewCount="153" Body="&lt;p&gt;Throughout the beta, we need members from the site whose focus is to engage the community, both in community-building issues and site management. That's why we select a few members from each community to act as temporary, provisional Moderators. You can read about the program here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/07/moderator-pro-tempore/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderators Pro Tempore&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am pleased to announce that these members have stepped up and generously volunteered their time to help us assure that each community’s issues are properly addressed:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/262&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/flair/262.png&quot; alt=&quot;hoc_age&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/127/glenh7&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/flair/127.png&quot; alt=&quot;fredley&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/80/trevor-archibald&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/flair/80.png&quot; alt=&quot;Sam Whited&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We want to make this site a huge success, and these members are great examples of exactly the type of people we need to make this site succeed. Please welcome them for the hard work and time they contribute.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Did I overlook anyone?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Almost certainly&lt;/strong&gt;. There are members who are actively involved and very deserving of recognition. My failure to account for everyone this early on is in &lt;em&gt;no way&lt;/em&gt; a slight against them. Ideally, Moderators are elected by the community and that's why we eventually hold elections.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of all, be respectful and understanding of the Moderators Pro Tem. Members of your community are volunteering their time and learning on the job. It’s a learning experience for everyone. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Update - June 2015:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sam Whited has resigned his moderator diamond. We wish him the best and thank him for his excellent service!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In his place, another community member has volunteered to step up to the plate. Please join me in welcoming:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/25/nick-udell&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/users/flair/25.png&quot; alt=&quot;Nick Udell&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="37" LastEditorUserId="37" LastEditDate="2015-06-16T19:53:03.387" LastActivityDate="2015-06-17T08:20:38.887" Title="Moderator Pro Tem Announcement" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="104" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="102" CreationDate="2015-02-16T22:04:07.300" Score="0" Body="&lt;h2&gt;It's more &quot;a wiki thing.&quot;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not every question about coffee is on topic for a Stack site about coffee: Stacks want to be neatly-sorted piles of questions and answers wherein &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;experts solve actual problems that people are facing&lt;/a&gt;. The Stack Exchange has little interest in duplicating services other parts of the Internet are already good at providing, and is structured so that often those services just plain don't work here. This is why &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/06/optimizing-for-pearls-not-sand/&quot;&gt;we are choosey about the questions we get&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets turn to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help&quot;&gt;Help Center&lt;/a&gt; and see what it has to say about how question structure helps accomplish Stack goals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Help Center lists some flags indicating that a question might be a poor fit for the site. If a potential question hits more than one of the flags, that's a sign it's likely not gonna work out here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;To prevent your question from being flagged and possibly removed, avoid asking subjective questions where …&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;every answer is equally valid&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;there is no actual problem to be solved&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help/dont-ask&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A list of coffees would make every answer equally valid, and there's no actual problem being solved. That breaks our voting system, making it impossible for our answers to be neatly sorted by the groupmind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now lets look at signs of a &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Have you thoroughly searched for an answer before asking your question?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;if you give us details and context, we can provide a useful answer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help/how-to-ask&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second bullet point there reinforces the idea that questions should have problems they're trying to solve: without a particular situation the querent faces, details and context for useful answers are impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the first bullet point really hits the thing on the nose: the Stack is a place to ask experts to leverage their education and experience in a field to solve problems we can't solve ourselves. &lt;strong&gt;The Stack is not a place to ask experts to do simple research for us.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For further reading, I suggest &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.gaming.stackexchange.com/q/997&quot;&gt;Repositories&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/57383/244929&quot;&gt;Polling, Recommendations and subjective-ish stuff&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/117312/244929&quot;&gt;Questions with educational value&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.rpg.stackexchange.com/q/4805/4398&quot;&gt;Is trivia on topic?&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.rpg.stackexchange.com/q/3398/4398&quot;&gt;What's so problematic about a recommendation question having potentially hundreds of answers, anyway?&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And, of course, there's always &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_coffee_drinks&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Wikipedia's List of Coffee Drinks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="92" LastEditorUserId="92" LastEditDate="2015-02-16T22:43:26.437" LastActivityDate="2015-02-16T22:43:26.437" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="105" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="102" CreationDate="2015-02-17T00:59:50.700" Score="0" Body="&lt;h1&gt;Don't even try to answer it.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yep, those type of questions are off-topic and there is no real problem. You want a list of coffee types, go up to Google and/or Wikipedia and look it up. To answer your question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;That is a wiki question, Downvote it and flag it, no questions asked&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That's basically what you should do. Seriously, that question would not survive 5 minutes without at least 3 dowvotes, unless it was deleted. :-) I hope this answers your question!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T00:59:50.700" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="106" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="102" CreationDate="2015-02-17T01:12:12.230" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I disagree with the other answers. These sorts of questions (if properly worded) are certainly on topic. The way they should be done is by marking the question as community wiki so that everyone can answer in one place instead of having hundreds of different answers with individual names in them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T01:12:12.230" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="107" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="97" CreationDate="2015-02-17T05:03:13.383" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I dabbled some.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/NCOpL.gif&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="308" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T05:03:13.383" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="108" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="1109" CreationDate="2015-02-17T11:08:53.183" Score="6" ViewCount="49" Body="&lt;p&gt;Can I ask questions associated with caffeine, like what are different sources of caffeine?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or that kind of questions are off-topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="294" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T14:40:00.937" Title="Can I ask questions just about caffeine?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="109" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="108" CreationDate="2015-02-17T11:53:55.993" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;It depends really. Caffeine is many things. It is a chemical. It is a psychoactive drug. It is a taste. It is a component of coffee, tea and other drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you've got a question about caffeine, have a think about what context you're asking it in, and who might be able to answer. Would a chemist be the type of person who might know the answer? Take it over to &lt;a href=&quot;http://chemistry.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Chemistry.SE&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If it's a direct health question (related to caffeine in general and not specifically coffee - which contains other chemicals that have other effects), this might not be the right place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your example &quot;What are different sources of caffeine?&quot; is a bad question for SE in general, as it's kinda open ended and the answer would just be a big list. Even questions like &quot;What plants produce caffeine?&quot; might do better on &lt;a href=&quot;http://gardening.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;Gardening.SE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your question is about caffeine in relation to coffee in any way, it's probably &lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; topic though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's still early days, we've got a long way to go in terms of finding and testing the limits of our scope. If you're not sure, post anyway. It's much better to discuss actual questions than hash imaginary ones out on meta :-)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T11:53:55.993" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1108" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="103" CreationDate="2015-02-17T13:46:24.933" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since there wasn't a nomination post, I think it'd be nice if we introduce ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm fredley, I've been a mod on Arqade for a year already, and a member of Stack Exchange for nearly five years. I live and work in London, and my office currently has no coffee making facilities in it at all :-(&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/124495&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/flair/124495.png&quot; width=&quot;208&quot; height=&quot;58&quot; alt=&quot;profile for Tom Medley on Stack Exchange, a network of free, community-driven Q&amp;amp;A sites&quot; title=&quot;profile for Tom Medley on Stack Exchange, a network of free, community-driven Q&amp;amp;A sites&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At home, I make my coffee with my trusty Bialetti moka pot, but I've had espresso machines in the past and hope to have another soon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to moderation, I'm a quality fanatic - I will edit a lot, but do call me out if you think I've gone too far. During waking hours (GMT) I'm usually hailable in chat.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of growing the community, I believe if we can create great content, people will find us, and if we're welcoming they'll stay. If we can keep it up for the next few months as the beta proceeds, I don't see why we can't carry this site to graduation and beyond!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/Y0sp3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastEditorUserId="127" LastEditDate="2015-02-17T16:31:15.880" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T16:31:15.880" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1109" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="108" CreationDate="2015-02-17T14:08:37.097" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;An adjunct to @fredley's answer: You can ask questions &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;associated with coffee.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/tour&quot;&gt;The tour&lt;/a&gt; sums it in the first sentence:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coffee Stack Exchange&lt;/strong&gt; is a question and answer site for people interested in all aspects of producing and consuming coffee. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That's it.  If your question doesn't involve producing or consuming coffee, it's questionable.  Though coffee (does, generally) happen to contain caffeine, caffeine (itself) is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the topic of the site. Some other examples: Cola is off-topic, even though the beverage has a similar color. &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/q/91/262&quot;&gt;Tea is off-topic&lt;/a&gt; (see also &lt;a href=&quot;http://discuss.area51.stackexchange.com/q/12394/120719&quot;&gt;original discussion&lt;/a&gt;), even though it has other similarities. Questions that discuss coffee, and happen to mention other topics (e.g., tea or cola) are fine -- &lt;em&gt;if they discuss coffee&lt;/em&gt; as their primary topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, we &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; need to put some content at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help/on-topic&quot;&gt;help/on-topic page&lt;/a&gt;.  This is the canonical location for detailed information about what is on-topic at a given site; it's shortcut-linkable in comments from &lt;code&gt;[help/on-topic]&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastEditorUserId="262" LastEditDate="2015-02-17T14:40:00.937" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T14:40:00.937" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1110" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="103" CreationDate="2015-02-17T15:37:53.617" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I shall follow suit!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm hoc_age, and I like coffee and Science. I enjoy learning and understanding the nature of the (coffee) universe; to that end, I like explanations that have a basis in demonstrable fact  (though &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/a/79/262&quot;&gt;not exclusively&lt;/a&gt; :). I experiment with different coffee preparation and enjoyment methods as a vehicle. I also like cooking (and Science) and contribute to &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Seasoned Advice&lt;/a&gt;. I have a tendency to be pedantic and verbose, but I also try to be conscientious and receptive: if you don't like what I say or how I say it, please tell me! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More broadly, I'm a relatively new &quot;active&quot; user (~1 year) to Stack Exchange. I am a huge proponent of the &lt;em&gt;learning-based&lt;/em&gt; approach to Stack Exchange, and am a big believer in effort and engagement in a community. I wish I could wear my &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2015/01/so-long-winter-bash-2014/&quot;&gt;&quot;Warm Welcome&quot; hat&lt;/a&gt; year 'round. See &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackoverflow.com/q/252149/3562032&quot;&gt;my original meta-missive&lt;/a&gt; for more of my philosophy. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm rarely the &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/q/9731/262760&quot;&gt;FGITW&lt;/a&gt;, so I (&lt;em&gt;try&lt;/em&gt; to...) try to take the opposite approach: make a smaller number of higher-quality posts. I originally heard this philosophy as pertains to scientific papers; the original author was lamenting (a perception) that scientists were trying to write as many papers as possible, as quickly as possible (for any number of perceived reasons: funding, relevance, legitimacy, pressure, e-peen, ...) I.e., without as much regard for their content, quality, or profoundness. SE is structured to enhance and enforce quality. Let's make this the best coffee-site possible!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-02-17T15:37:53.617" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1112" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="1115" CreationDate="2015-02-17T23:26:05.253" Score="0" ViewCount="48" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am not trying to be greedy here. I have answer this [question][1] long ago (probably during private beta). It had 150 rep as a bounty by Nathan and it was never awarded in during the seven day period. The grace period has past by and this is suppose to happen according to &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help/bounty&quot;&gt;the bounty section in the Help Center&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If you do not award the bounty within 24 hours of the bounty period ending, half the bounty value will be automatically awarded to the top voted answer posted after the bounty start, provided it has a score of at least 2. If no new answer matches this requirement, no reputation will be awarded at all, and the reputation used on the bounty will be lost forever.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please notice this part for specificly:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If you do not award the bounty within 24 hours of the bounty period ending, half the bounty value will be automatically awarded to the top voted answer posted after the bounty start, provided it has a score of at least 2.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have the current highest voted answer with a score of +8 yet I didn't get any of the rep (75 to be exact). The half-bounty was actually awarded to therewillbecoffee's answer instead. That answer has a score of +5 at the moment. So my question is why didn't I get any of the 75 rep? My answer has matched all the requirements listed, so I don't quite understand. Did the OP manually award it? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="37" LastEditDate="2015-02-18T23:06:34.147" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T23:06:34.147" Title="How Come I Didn't Get The Half-Bounty" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;bounty&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="1113" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="103" CreationDate="2015-02-18T00:15:40.373" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yay — my power's back on! After a day in the dark, I can finally introduce myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm Sam; some of you may already know me from other sites in the SE network. I've also got the diamond over on &lt;a href=&quot;https://tor.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Tor.SE&lt;/a&gt;, and occasionally go on ask/answer binges over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://tex.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;TeX.SE&lt;/a&gt;. I currently hail from Atlanta, GA (but not for long as I'm moving to Austin, TX this very weekend to start a new job in software engineering).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have a french press and espresso machine sitting on my desk at all times (and a tea kettle on the stove heating up water for the french press, of course), and generally prefer my coffee black. My favorite roasts are &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.batdorfcoffee.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Batdorf &amp;amp; Bronson&lt;/a&gt;'s &quot;Dancing Goats&quot; (makes a seriously good cup of espresso) and anything from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://atlantacoffeeroasters.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Atlanta Coffee Roasters&lt;/a&gt; in the press pot or on drip (I used to practically live in their store-front / coffee shop back when I worked from home). I also recently did a thru-hike of the Appalachian trail, where I learned that it's always possible to make cowboy coffee in the woods if you try hard enough.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm looking forward to working with you all to build a great community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/141416&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/users/flair/141416.png&quot; width=&quot;208&quot; height=&quot;58&quot; alt=&quot;profile for Sam Whited on Stack Exchange, a network of free, community-driven Q&amp;amp;A sites&quot; title=&quot;profile for Sam Whited on Stack Exchange, a network of free, community-driven Q&amp;amp;A sites&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastEditorUserId="80" LastEditDate="2015-02-18T02:16:38.327" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T02:16:38.327" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1114" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="97" CreationDate="2015-02-18T10:43:01.653" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/BYA6p.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Image is by some SE Meta user Attribution://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/138755/stack-overflow-mug&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="132" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T10:43:01.653" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="1115" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1112" CreationDate="2015-02-18T13:23:48.530" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;If I recall correctly, I believe you answered the question before Nathan added the bounty. I know that @therewillbecoffee answered after you did.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the SE thought process is as follows. If a user attaches a bounty it is because they are not convinced with any of the existing answers. Thus, if the user who added the bounty never awards it, the partial award goes to the best answer that came after the bounty was created.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="23" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T13:23:48.530" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="1116" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="97" CreationDate="2015-02-18T20:22:50.053" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;How about coffee beans with a magnifying glass? This could connote the metaphor of examining coffee more closely. Here's &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shutterstock.com/pic-129990014/stock-photo-man-s-hand-keeps-magnifying-glass-over-the-coffee-beans.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;an example from Shutterstock&lt;/a&gt; of what I'm talking about, because I'm not much of a photographer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T20:22:50.053" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1117" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-18T20:31:30.993" Score="4" ViewCount="43" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some SE sites have a community blag &amp;mdash; do we have one yet that we could start publishing on? Do we have to wait until we're out of beta for it or something?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of our users have valuable stories they might like to share, and often do, about their experiences with coffee, especially from stuff they've found on this site! It might be valuable to make the community blog available for people to share stuff independent of any need to answer a question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="47" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T21:04:56.373" Title="Do we have a blog? (If not, when do we get it?)" Tags="&lt;support&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1118" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1117" CreationDate="2015-02-18T21:04:56.373" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/244467/were-no-longer-starting-new-individual-site-community-blogs-heres-why&quot;&gt;never&lt;/a&gt;, I'm afraid. This doesn't mean we can't have an unofficial one, or start a community on Medium or something equivalent. It would be good to discuss what the community thinks we should do (if anything) on social media! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2015-02-18T21:04:56.373" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="1119" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="1120" CreationDate="2015-02-20T02:07:25.220" Score="-2" ViewCount="51" Body="&lt;p&gt;I personally think that moderators should have a fun way to introducing our new users to Coffee.SE. Seriously, it is getting old with this similar phrase:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Welcome to Coffee.SE! Please remember to take the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/tour&quot;&gt;tour&lt;/a&gt; and earn your next badge of honor! Please take a quick visit to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/help&quot;&gt;Help Center&lt;/a&gt; to help improve the quality of future your posts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lots of mods use a similar phrase to introduce new users on whatever SE site they are on &#xA;(Sam Whited, you know what I mean :-) ). It starts to get old, then boring, and finally just plain annoying. New users should receive a warm, meaningful welcome, not a robotic-like message implied to every new user. My question is, how should the Coffee Mods introduce our new users in a warm, friendly way without using the same message again and again? All suggestions are appreciated and don't be afraid to share your idea?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-20T02:27:11.800" Title="How Should A Coffee Moderator Introduce A New User" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="1120" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1119" CreationDate="2015-02-20T02:27:11.800" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;First off, a defense of messages like that one. Keep in mind that the welcome isn't for us, it's for the new user. Even if the same welcome message has been posted plenty of times and you're tired of it, it's the first time &lt;em&gt;they've&lt;/em&gt; seen it - that's why they're being welcomed! So it doesn't seem nearly so robotic to them as to you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, while making them feel welcomed is half the goal, letting them know about the ground rules is really important too. A lot of people expect discussion forums, and are really confused by the way StackExchange sites work the first time they visit. They post not-really-answers, they take downvotes personally, and so on. Pointing them to the tour/help at the first opportunity is an attempt to avoid this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So in my mind, the canned messages are fine. I might tweak the one you quoted a bit, but there's nothing wrong with something along those lines. If I wanted to go beyond that, I'd simply to throw in a specific comment as well - something very simple that I liked about their post, or a suggestion for improving it. But that's not always too easy, and I don't think there's anything wrong with just using the template.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, if you want more variety, why not just welcome them yourself?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The moderators don't own the site. Their primary job is to do the things that no one else can. This early in a beta, there's a little more in that category since there are fewer high-reputation users. But welcoming a new user? All you need to be able to do is comment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So if you want to contribute some variety, go for it. A variety of &lt;em&gt;users&lt;/em&gt; doing the welcoming is perhaps even more meaningful than a variety of messages: it demonstrates that the site is a community site, not one kept carefully under the control of a few moderators. Just keep in mind &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; you're doing it: to make them feel welcome, yes, but also to help them learn how the site works so they can make good contributions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="230" LastActivityDate="2015-02-20T02:27:11.800" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="1121" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-02-21T14:14:43.257" Score="2" ViewCount="101" Body="&lt;p&gt;A lot of sites have a special motto. It is usually funny, interesting and catchy. I think we should have a catchy motto too. So what do you think our motto should be? Make it as awesome, catchy, and more interesting as you can! All ideas are okay!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="75" LastEditDate="2015-02-24T21:37:00.993" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T17:00:22.233" Title="What should be our motto?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="1122" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1121" CreationDate="2015-02-21T19:54:32.503" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;A few thoughts: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Coffee.SE: overthinking coffee since 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; coffee nerds learn about &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; coffee.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Coffee + Science: FUN&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Serious coffee questions need serious answers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-02-21T19:54:32.503" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1123" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1121" CreationDate="2015-02-21T23:48:52.507" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a few suggestions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Serving Coffee and Knowledge Since 2015&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee.SE - Official Q/A for Coffee-ers!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee + Knowledge = Coffee.SE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-21T23:48:52.507" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1125" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="80" CreationDate="2015-02-25T01:02:52.283" Score="-2" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, no question should not have that tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is weird having that tag when the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;site&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; itself is about coffee. It's not an factor or aspect of coffee, it &lt;strong&gt;is&lt;/strong&gt; coffee. Having &quot;coffee&quot; is probably not acceptable. If you can't find the tag you need, get to 125 rep and make a new one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like the others, people can &lt;em&gt;include&lt;/em&gt; coffee in their tags for more detail. I'm perfectly fine with that and so are the mods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-25T01:02:52.283" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1126" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="1127" CreationDate="2015-02-25T01:07:08.577" Score="0" ViewCount="33" Body="&lt;p&gt;I recently got 2 rep for having an approved edit on the &quot;flavor&quot; badge as shown here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;+10  Are there any disadvantages to shade grown coffee?&#xA;+10  How hot should the water be for instant coffee?&#xA;+2   flavor tag wiki&#xA;+2   brewing-process tag wiki&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I checked the tag out and hoped to see my edit shown on the flavor badge. Then I found this weird quote when I clicked the &quot;flavor&quot; tag:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;The flavor tag has no wiki summary, can you help us create it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What?! I just got an approved edit and it says there has been no edit or current summary.I clicked on it and it shows a piece of my summary (okay, not, hoc_age also edited this one plus brewing-process). Why isn't the tag summary for flavor showing properly? The brewing-process wiki (which I edited) was approved and is visible:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;The process of brewing coffee, hot or cold. (hoc_age edited it so it is shorter than my original) &#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastActivityDate="2015-02-25T02:23:08.233" Title="Where's The Tag Wiki for Flavor?" Tags="&lt;bug&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;tag-wiki&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1127" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1126" CreationDate="2015-02-25T02:23:08.233" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;You suggested content/edit for the &lt;em&gt;flavor tag wiki&lt;/em&gt;, but it looks like you did &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; suggest content/edit for the &lt;em&gt;flavor tag wiki &lt;strong&gt;excerpt&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. That's the reason that there was no content there: no one had yet put any content in the excerpt.  There are two different fields for the tag wiki: one for the &quot;excerpt&quot; (short version) and one for the main tag wiki.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the history of the universe, it looks like you suggested tag wiki edits to the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;temperature tag wiki&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;temperature tag wiki excerpt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;brewing-process tag wiki&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;brewing-process tag wiki excerpt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;bean-varieties tag wiki&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;bean-varieties tag wiki excerpt&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;flavor tag wiki&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I.e., you suggested an edit to the &quot;flavor tag wiki&quot;, but you did not submit a suggested edit for the &quot;flavor tag wiki &lt;em&gt;excerpt&lt;/em&gt;.&quot; I put in a placeholder for the &quot;flavor tag wiki excerpt&quot;; feel free to suggest an edit if you'd like.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think everyone can view the history of the tag wikis and excerpts; see &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/posts/1560/revisions&quot;&gt;the flavor tag wiki excerpt history here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for proposing content for the tag wikis!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-02-25T02:23:08.233" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1128" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-03-03T14:43:49.033" Score="4" ViewCount="50" Body="&lt;p&gt;This question is spurred by a recent question on the main site: &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/1579/why-does-some-coffee-hit-me-harder-than-other-coffee&quot;&gt;Why does some coffee &amp;quot;hit me&amp;quot; harder than other coffee?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The original (see &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/1579/why-does-some-coffee-hit-me-harder-than-other-coffee&quot;&gt;the history&lt;/a&gt;) was specifically about one brand; it received several close-votes for &quot;opinion-based&quot; reason.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I edited the question in an attempt to make it &quot;more objective&quot; -- e.g., what affects coffee's stimulation? I provided an answer about the tangible aspects of caffeine, which turned out to be more of a survey, predominantly with links to other questions about factors that affect caffeine content in coffee.  The question was closed, but it has now received re-open votes, so it looks like we have disagreement (at least in part, a good thing)!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Such &quot;survey&quot; questions and answers are not always on-topic, and are often controversial (another example is &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/24557728/does-any-c-library-implement-c11-threads-for-gnu-linux&quot;&gt;this question of mine from Stack Overflow, in which I summarized a handful of other questions&lt;/a&gt;). That question was closed and subsequently re-opened, meaning that it probably received several close- and open-votes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I happen to (personally) appreciate those kind of question/answer when appropriate; I value them as an index and summary of several questions, often comparisons of (or distinguishing between) questions within a certain tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To the extent that this represents an example of a &quot;survey of other questions&quot; answer: &lt;strong&gt;Are such &quot;survey&quot; answers (and the related question) reasonable? Or should such questions be discouraged, and limit to more narrow, on-point questions about a similar topic?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-03-05T17:20:21.513" Title="Do we allow summary-like questions and answers?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1129" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1128" CreationDate="2015-03-03T17:45:29.563" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;tldr; keep it case by case, let the community decide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can't speak for everyone but I gave one of the initial close votes and also gave the first re-open vote.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I felt that in this case your edit accomplished two things. It played down company brands in the question and made it answerable. I may have also had the bias of wanting to not reject someone's first question to the site if it could be saved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, I can see problems with opening the door to all &quot;summary-like&quot; questions, many of which may instead belong as wikis or just good chat discussions. Instead I think we just need to weigh each question as it comes in. Maybe eventually we'll have a list specifically for coffee.se to show which borderline questions survive and which don't.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="23" LastActivityDate="2015-03-03T17:45:29.563" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1130" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1121" CreationDate="2015-03-03T21:39:13.010" Score="-4" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep calm and drink coffee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/Sr29a.png&quot; alt=&quot;Keep calm; drink coffee&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;sup&gt;Original image &lt;a href=&quot;http://sd.keepcalm-o-matic.co.uk/i/keep-calm-and-drink-coffee-400.png&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="179" LastActivityDate="2015-03-03T21:39:13.010" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1131" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1128" CreationDate="2015-03-05T16:30:26.660" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Setting aside the &quot;primarily opinion based&quot; reason to close Questions, the concern raised by &quot;summary-like&quot; questions is a potential need to manage a set of nearly-duplicate Questions, varying only in minor details but all asking essentially the same thing.  Joel had &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/the-wikipedia-of-long-tail-programming-questions/&quot;&gt;an early blog post&lt;/a&gt; about this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Math.SE we might treat these as &quot;abstract duplicates&quot;, and a list of them, &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.math.stackexchange.com/questions/1868/list-of-generalizations-of-common-questions&quot;&gt;List of Generalizations of Common Questions&lt;/a&gt; is maintained on &lt;code&gt;meta&lt;/code&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, we get a lot of posts asking things very similar to: why is 1+2+3+... = -1/12?  (It makes a little more sense than one might suspect at first glance.)  Rather than run through the basics each time, it was thought expedient to have one well-answered post of this kind and then be able to refer new Questions to that one as an &quot;abstract duplicate&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Something of the kind seems to be in the spirit of &quot;summary-like&quot; questions.  Although it is early days, we might see such repetitive trends emerging.  If so, I'd recommend keeping track of those with a &lt;code&gt;meta&lt;/code&gt; thread, so that finding those &quot;canonical&quot; answers can be easy enough (and it would admit some discussion on &lt;code&gt;meta&lt;/code&gt; whether a topic deserves &quot;summary&quot; treatment).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="34" LastEditorUserId="34" LastEditDate="2015-03-05T17:20:21.513" LastActivityDate="2015-03-05T17:20:21.513" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1132" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-04-11T02:59:36.357" Score="6" ViewCount="59" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I asked in the main site this question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/q/1724/157&quot;&gt;Is there an alternative to Kopi Luwak in terms of taste and aroma?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and was almost immediately flagged as off-topic because of being a &quot;product recommendation&quot; one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even in the case that such a question indeed is a &quot;product recommendation question&quot;, I think it relates to this answer:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/a/38/157&quot;&gt;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/a/38/157&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;in the sense that my question points specifically to a very unique kind of coffee, one that is produced just in a limited region of the planet, and since its features are very special, I really don't think that a plethora of answers will be received, and is very likely that the one or two that may appear will all point towards the same direction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Said all this, I expect the opinion of the community, in order to keep the question open or close it right away.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finally, I made a new question.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, I've just rephrased the question with a new one, following @hoc_age recommendations:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/q/1760/157&quot;&gt;What does Kopi Luwak taste like?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="157" LastEditorUserId="157" LastEditDate="2015-04-18T15:32:50.963" LastActivityDate="2015-04-18T15:32:50.963" Title="Asking for an alternative for Kopi Luwak was flagged as off-topic" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;close-reasons&gt;&lt;product-recommendation&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="1133" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1132" CreationDate="2015-04-15T14:20:39.447" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;My take on this is that the &quot;product recommendation&quot; might be a little misleading. Let's focus instead about what you're really asking, and what type of answer you're looking for. It seems that there's quite a bit of interest in the topic of &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kopi_Luwak&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Kopi Luwak&lt;/a&gt;, because there are several questions about it and much discussion. I think there's a lot of room for interesting Q&amp;amp;A related to this topic!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fundamentally, &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/help/how-to-ask&quot;&gt;what's your question or what are you trying to solve&lt;/a&gt;? From your initial question, it sounds like...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;you have never tried Kopi Luwak;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;you don't know how it tastes,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;you are unable or unwilling to try it;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;you are looking for an alternative.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are any of those a more fundamental question that you have?  &lt;strong&gt;How about changing the question to, &quot;What does Kopi Luwak taste like?&quot;&lt;/strong&gt; Then you can also ask in the body of the question, or infer from the answer, &quot;What other coffees taste like it?&quot;  Though similar in concept, I think &quot;how does it taste&quot; comes across better.  What do you think? I'd be happy to re-articulate the question with you, or un-lock it if you change it around.  For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does Kopi Luwak taste like?&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;br&gt;I have never had the opportunity to try Kopi Luwak, but I'd like to know how it tastes. How is does the taste differ from more traditionally processed coffee from the same region? Are there other coffees that have similar tasting notes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or something like that. That said, &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/a/141/262&quot;&gt;this answer says Kopi Luwak is delicious&lt;/a&gt;, and has some descriptions, but there's probably room for another question on the topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another question might be something more like &quot;&lt;em&gt;Why&lt;/em&gt; does Kopi Luwak taste different?&quot; For example, what is it about the Kopi Luwak digestion process that changes the beans? What happens to the beans during digestion (e.g., protein digestion)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There might also be room for a question about &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Black_Ivory_coffee&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Black Ivory Coffee&lt;/a&gt;, which is apparently coffee digestively &quot;processed&quot; in a similar way by rescued elephants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-04-15T14:20:39.447" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1134" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-04-15T15:18:58.147" Score="9" ViewCount="122" Body="&lt;p&gt;Okay, Coffee beta-ers! We're 75 days into beta. How are we doing?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/61013/coffee&quot;&gt;the Coffee Beta Stats on Area51&lt;/a&gt;, certain things are not looking good:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Need more questions!  &quot;Healthy&quot; is about 10 questions per day; we average less than 2.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Need more users!  &quot;Healthy&quot; is over 1000 visits per day. We have about 85 visits per day, which I think means unique users/IP-addresses.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can we get more participation?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; As @RobertCartiano points out in comments, there's nothing special about the upcoming 90-day threshold, it's just how the stats happen to be listed/pegged-against in Area51. Thanks very much for the link -- an excellent read. Nonetheless, it still seems like a good time-frame to check up to see if we could encourage more participation. Or will it simply take more time for a niche site like this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastEditorUserId="262" LastEditDate="2015-04-16T01:00:24.320" LastActivityDate="2015-07-24T17:50:27.777" Title="How do we get more participation?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="5" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="1135" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1134" CreationDate="2015-04-23T14:54:29.663" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've seen other sites have some success via regular events, e.g. &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.worldbuilding.stackexchange.com/questions/1758/should-we-have-weekly-topic-challenges&quot;&gt;World Building&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.codereview.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/community-challenge&quot;&gt;Code Reviews&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively we can cross our fingers and hope for a major new coffee product, for which we can quickly position ourselves as the de-facto help resource, but that seems like wishful thinking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However if one does come about (or some other, similarly major coffee-related event occurs), then we should be sure to position ourselves as the best resource out there by quickly producing a comprehensive set of questions and answers on all facets of the new subject.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One thing to note is that more questions will tend to lead to more users, and vice versa, as more questions lead more people to the site via google and more users post more questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-04-23T14:54:29.663" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1136" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1134" CreationDate="2015-04-27T13:49:31.280" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think we need to encourage more product specific questions. I think we're losing questions where users want to ask a question relating to their specific set up, whether it be machine, or grinder or other coffee making equipment. The questions we have already have on brewing methods etc are great, but take a look at any other &lt;strong&gt;successful&lt;/strong&gt; coffee site and you'll see 9/10 times they're split into sub sections on machine manufacturer as well as different brewing methods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, we can't just lump all 'espresso' questions together and discourage questions which want to know the specifics on one machine/brand. An entry level £50 espresso machine is a whole different ball game to one costing £1000+, and believe me people who are into their coffee will drop that kind of money easily, and will want answers on their specific set up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is just my opinion, but I have been put off asking questions I've had because they're very much related to my machine and grinder set up. I think more questions on specific machines would get more search engine hits and therefore grow the site quicker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="121" LastActivityDate="2015-04-27T13:49:31.280" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1137" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1121" CreationDate="2015-05-06T11:31:04.670" Score="-1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Coffee SE - Jittery with knowledge&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-05-06T11:31:04.670" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1138" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-05-14T02:19:34.513" Score="5" ViewCount="22" Body="&lt;p&gt;Australian coffee shops have been taking to stocking their own &lt;a href=&quot;http://keepcup.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Keepcups&lt;/a&gt; in recent years, often marked with the coffee shop's brand. For those unaware &amp;mdash; I don't know what their presence is like outside Australia &amp;mdash; this is a Melbourne-based company that produces reusable coffee cups in glass or plastic, like this one:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/DNBms.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a glass keepcup.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have some questions about my own keepcup and maintaining it. This isn't about coffee itself, but this is intimately a coffee product, and I'm going to find my expertise on keepcups within the coffee drinker world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do questions about Keepcups fit here, or not?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="47" LastEditorUserId="47" LastEditDate="2015-05-14T02:29:42.537" LastActivityDate="2015-05-14T11:56:52.730" Title="Can I ask about Keepcups here?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;support&gt;&lt;topicality&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1139" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-05-14T08:36:07.627" Score="2" ViewCount="33" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm thinking questions such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Kopi Luwak?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do I make a Cappuccino?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simple questions that might not even be asked by the user base until the site has grown a little, but might bring in more beginners.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-06-22T22:30:02.573" Title="Should we produce canonical community wiki questions and answers for basic topics?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1140" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1138" CreationDate="2015-05-14T08:36:56.437" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would say yes, since they are intrinsically related to coffee, and would be a useful addition to a repository of coffee knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-05-14T08:36:56.437" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1141" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1138" CreationDate="2015-05-14T11:56:52.730" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes, if you use it in conjunction with storing, brewing or consuming coffee - I think it's on-topic. I've got some porcelain stuff I'd &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; to get coffee stains out of, and intend to ask about that as soon as I find some time. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-05-14T11:56:52.730" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1142" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1139" CreationDate="2015-05-14T12:15:06.060" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I haven't seen that many duplicates; canonical questions are really the answer to that. By taking an existing question / answer and putting &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; someone would want to know about a frequently searched question, you can obviate the need for people to continue to ask. But they do, which is why duplicates asked just a tad differently all pointing to the canonical work so well. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't think we have the problem yet, even though I'm wondering how much ground we &lt;em&gt;haven't&lt;/em&gt; covered on the topic :P&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;End of anything official in this response.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What I've been kicking around is the idea of self-answered questions about my own gear, e.g. &quot;How easy is the Breville Barista Express to operate?&quot; or &quot;how long does the niju-glass double-walled press hold a constant temp?&quot; where I'd just write about my experience with owning and using this stuff. I'd definitely be interested in someone from &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; community talking about a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lamarzocco.com/en/headline-news/news-press/item/528-eater-us-online-source-for-people-who-care-about-dining-and-drinking-test-drives-the-linea-mini.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;La Marzocco Linea Mini&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This serves a big piece of what people look for in a site like this, &lt;em&gt;should I spend my hard earned cash on [thing]?&lt;/em&gt;. It also unlocks a lot of additional content for us. It's not 'shopping', or 'what should I buy' - it's &quot;I have this thing and have useful information to share about it&quot;. It just has to be shared in the form of a question. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't know. I haven't given it a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of thought, I mention it only because signs that folks are getting a bit bored are starting to emerge :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2015-05-14T12:15:06.060" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="1143" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1139" CreationDate="2015-05-18T01:30:45.453" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I like the question and was thinking more on it... so I decided to expand on part of my comment on the question into this answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My first thought with most of these is, &quot;What have other Stack Exchange sites done in this situation?&quot; I wrote a meta-question about a somewhat-similar topic of &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/q/1128/262&quot;&gt;summary-like questions&lt;/a&gt;. I especially liked &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/a/1131/262&quot;&gt;this answer from hardmath&lt;/a&gt; about how &lt;a href=&quot;http://math.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Math.SE&lt;/a&gt; handles some of those &quot;canonical&quot; topics.(Aside: &lt;a href=&quot;http://math.stackexchange.com/questions/39802/why-does-123-cdots-frac112&quot;&gt;His particular example&lt;/a&gt; is fasinating and blew my mind. :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think there's value in letting good answers to such topics &quot;happen organically,&quot; even though that's somewhat less satisfying in certain ways than getting some good, fundamental answer to some good, fundamental question committed into the annals of the Internet(s). That said, I saw some confusion (partly my own) about a topic, so I wrote a self-Q/A about &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/1564/what-do-the-terms-extraction-and-strength-mean&quot;&gt;What do the terms extraction and strength mean?&lt;/a&gt; My goal there was to clear up some terms that I didn't understand and that were being used somewhat inconsistently or imprecisely. Especially in those cases, I'm certainly in favor of penning a good Q/A.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, I think having some &quot;softball&quot; questions every once in a while, even if duplicate, is healthy. If a new user to the site gets hooked by giving a solid answer to a question, that's a great &quot;gateway&quot; to this community. Having fundamental topics that are &quot;still open&quot; might be a good hook for a new user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another take on this is that some questions that are on-topic for the site might be already answered well other places. For example, if I search for how to make a cup of coffee in an auto-drip coffeemaker, I think I'd find a very large number of answers that are very adequate... therefore, they don't need to be &quot;asked&quot; here as such. That said, I'd be totally happy if someone earnestly asked something like that and got an earnest, helpful answer from this community. I hope we will be so lucky as to be &quot;the&quot; coffee reference site at some point in the future! :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-05-18T01:30:45.453" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1144" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-05-20T12:00:37.647" Score="1" ViewCount="18" Body="&lt;p&gt;The following question is under review for being closed as too broad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here's the question: &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/1856/coffee-on-daily-basis&quot;&gt;Coffee on daily basis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would like to know what the community thinks about this. &lt;strong&gt;Is it too broad, or not?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also this question has a poor format in my opinion. Here is how I believe it should be structured:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ask if coffee on a daily basis is healthy or not.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Based on that result, ask why or why not it is healthy or unhealthy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Which still may be quite broad)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am interested to know the community's opinion on this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="225" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-05-21T13:18:42.197" LastActivityDate="2015-05-21T13:18:42.197" Title="I'm on the fence about closing this question for the reason &quot;too broad&quot;" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;close-reasons&gt;&lt;vote-to-close&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1145" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-05-21T10:58:11.573" Score="4" ViewCount="28" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've seen other sites have some success drawing in and retaining users via regular community challenge events, e.g. &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.worldbuilding.stackexchange.com/questions/1758/should-we-have-weekly-topic-challenges&quot;&gt;World Building&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.codereview.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/community-challenge&quot;&gt;Code Review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since our participation is waning, should we consider doing something similar?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those not in the know, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/240634/how-do-weekly-topic-challenges-work&quot;&gt;community challenge&lt;/a&gt; works like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Users suggest various topics or themes. For example, on Earth Science, suggestions have included antarctic and volcanology.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Everyone else upvotes topics or themes they like.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Each week, the highest-voted suggestion becomes the weekly topic challenge. A meta post is written up giving a brief summary of the&#xA;  idea (with the featured tag, hopefully), and at the end of the week,&#xA;  users who asked or answered one or more questions about that topic are&#xA;  recognized.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Repeat until everyone gets tired of the idea or everyone runs out of suggestions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Should we have these challenges, how often should we have them, and who should be in charge of them?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-06-17T08:30:07.677" Title="Should we have Community Challenges?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1146" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-06-01T20:18:25.330" Score="6" ViewCount="43" Body="&lt;p&gt;I recently asked &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com/q/1887/145&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt; about how to know what type of coffee to use in a recipe, and how to be able to tell whether the difference will be tasted in the final result. I happened to give a specific recipe example because I was concerned that the question would be too broad without it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I read &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/32/should-questions-about-recipes-involving-coffee-be-considered-off-topic&quot;&gt;Should questions about recipes involving coffee be considered off topic?&lt;/a&gt; before posting my answer and I was satisfied that my question was on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notably:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Coffee is a common ingredient in many popular deserts, and fits well here, &lt;strong&gt;as long as the 'gist' requires knowledge of not just cooking, but also coffee in order to answer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a question is on-topic on multiple sites, SE guidelines are that it can be posted on any of them. A question should only be migrated if it is &lt;strong&gt;definitely off-topic&lt;/strong&gt; on the site it is on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, my question got &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/questions/57923/will-there-be-a-noticeable-taste-difference-in-my-tiramisu-if-i-use-proper-coffe&quot;&gt;migrated to Seasoned Advice&lt;/a&gt;. Why? Was it because I provided a specific recipe instead of asking for a general approach? In my opinion my question could have been asked on either site, but &lt;strong&gt;I posted it here because I specifically wanted &lt;em&gt;coffee&lt;/em&gt; expertise&lt;/strong&gt; about how to prepare the coffee to use in the recipe, and how to determine what type to use. I know a fair bit about cooking, but I know very little about coffee. Is there any way I could have worded my quesion better to keep it on topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, why didn't I get a chance to edit it into shape before wham bam migration modhammer?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="145" LastActivityDate="2015-07-30T15:10:34.817" Title="Why was this question migrated without discussion?" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;scope&gt;&lt;specific-question&gt;&lt;migration&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="1147" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1146" CreationDate="2015-06-10T02:08:12.183" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I wasn't the one who migrated it, so I can't really give an authoritative answer. I do think an explanatory comment would've been helpful, for sure. I also think the question is a better fit for cooking, but perhaps it'd have been best to do nothing; usually we don't migrate questions that seem to be on the boundary between site scopes, and this question is definitely on the boundary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The rest of the answer discusses why I think it's a better fit on cooking, but do keep in mind I think it'd have been fine not to migrate too!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key point in my mind is also made in the other meta question you linked to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If it's more about cooking components, or cooking technique, then it's probably one for Seasoned Advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You say you wanted coffee expertise. But the question is about using coffee in a recipe, i.e. in the context of cooking. You're asking about one ingredient as part of a whole, about the combination of non-coffee flavors with other ingredients. People who are experts in making coffee are not necessarily experts in all of that, but people who are experts in cooking will know about how to use all kinds of ingredients, including coffee. It seems like a question that, despite your initial guess, is more about cooking than it is about coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I'm not sure exactly how you'd shape it up to make it more clearly seek coffee expertise. Coffee expertise will get you great answers about how much the flavor of different kinds of coffee differs, but not much about how obvious that'll be in the context of a tiramisu recipe. What were you trying to ask that cooking folks can't tell you?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, I'm not sure I'd make it a goal to keep it on coffee; it's not like it suffered because of the migration. When you're asking a question, the goal isn't to make sure it's on a particular site, it's just to get the best answers possible. I missed this when it showed up on cooking, but I think most likely the reason this didn't get any answers beyond the one that was migrated with it is that it's a pretty general question with a general answer, so it's hard to really give a more specific expert answer.  (If it &lt;em&gt;hadn't&lt;/em&gt; had that answer, you would doubtless have quickly gotten an answer on cooking, and been just as satisfied.) Nonetheless, I've added a few more thoughts!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, to emphasize, I think it'd have been reasonable to err on the side of doing nothing,  leave here, since you posted it here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="230" LastEditorUserId="230" LastEditDate="2015-06-10T02:26:15.140" LastActivityDate="2015-06-10T02:26:15.140" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="1148" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="103" CreationDate="2015-06-17T08:20:38.887" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;everybody!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm Nick, I'm new, and I love coffee, something that probably earns me the badge of &quot;traitor&quot; in my tea-loving home-nation of Britain. When it comes to coffee-related knowledge though, I'm a complete beginner, so expect me to be doing more asking than answering around here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm a scientist and programmer by day, and an independent game developer by night. If there are any occupations fuelled more by caffeine than those, let me know so I can add them to my CV.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm active on &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/&quot;&gt;StackOverflow&lt;/a&gt; and especially &lt;a href=&quot;http://codereview.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;CodeReview&lt;/a&gt;, and I'm very proud to call this wonderful site home. You can also find me sticking my oar in where it's not wanted over on various Area51 proposals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I prefer my coffees milky and frothy, but I'm slowly coming around to richer, stronger flavours. Who knows, maybe you'll make a black coffee drinker out of me yet!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-06-17T08:20:38.887" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1149" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1145" CreationDate="2015-06-17T08:30:07.677" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yes, we should have challenges.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Throwing my own oar in to suggest that yes, community challenges have a tendency to drive up participation, and help round out our knowledge base.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a newly minted moderator, I would be happy to take charge on this and organize the challenges, however if the community believes somebody else would be better for the job, I don't mind handing over the reigns either.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2015-06-17T08:30:07.677" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1150" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-06-21T19:46:05.747" Score="5" ViewCount="33" Body="&lt;p&gt;I contributed many example questions and discussions to the previous (failed) Area51 proposal for a Coffee site a few years ago. And I didn't even know about this one until seeing it on the SE dropdown menu &lt;em&gt;yesterday&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, bluntly, what did you guys do &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; the we did &lt;em&gt;wrong&lt;/em&gt;? And how come you didn't (or, why don't we go and ...) invite old committers from previous proposals?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The last proposal seemed to die when it was discovered that Coffee issues are all on-topic at Seasoned Advice. How did you guys jump that hurdle??&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="959" LastEditorUserId="959" LastEditDate="2015-06-21T21:55:02.330" LastActivityDate="2015-06-21T21:55:02.330" Title="Where did this site come from?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="1151" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1139" CreationDate="2015-06-22T22:30:02.573" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is a general trend away from CW, and my meta participation in meta.music.SE illustrates how I've learned this the hard way. But it does seem like CW's greatest feature is it greatest failure: no reputation points for participants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is particularly unappealing if you're writing something intending it to be a &quot;canonical&quot; answer. Yes, you may need help on some details. But the work you put into it should be rewarded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even on codegolf.SE where it used to be the policy that &quot;tips&quot; questions should be CW because they're not proper code challenges. When they changed it, removed all CW, and everybody started getting points ... nobody's complaining.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, &lt;strong&gt;Yes!&lt;/strong&gt; Write canonical answers. You can even write a fictitious question to lead-in to it. Share your knowledge. And enjoy the appreciation of your readers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="959" LastActivityDate="2015-06-22T22:30:02.573" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1152" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1121" CreationDate="2015-07-15T17:00:22.233" Score="-2" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The text below is the opinion of the answerer. Please don't read if&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;you're allergic to opinions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My suggestions: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where coffee and questions meet (A bit misleading?)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No, we do not serve &lt;strong&gt;decaf&lt;/strong&gt;. (Too funny?)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For coffee addicts who want points&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="132" LastActivityDate="2015-07-15T17:00:22.233" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1153" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1134" CreationDate="2015-07-24T17:50:27.777" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think getting more basic questions may help.  I was looking through the site today and besides what I perceive to be very few questions about home roasting, there are very few basic questions.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know there was &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/questions/1139/should-we-produce-canonical-community-wiki-questions-and-answers-for-basic-topic&quot;&gt;another meta question&lt;/a&gt; regarding this, but it sort of swayed back to another idea.  I think coffee.sx is going to get much more traffic from answers to questions like &quot;What is esspresso?&quot; that some of the more specialized (but still completely legitimate) questions currently out there.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="76" LastActivityDate="2015-07-24T17:50:27.777" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="1154" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1146" CreationDate="2015-07-30T15:10:34.817" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Though I do think it's good to post a question at &lt;em&gt;the site where it's most on-topic&lt;/em&gt;, there is an &lt;em&gt;official&lt;/em&gt;(-ish) &quot;policy on migration, at &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/10249/what-is-migration-and-how-does-it-work&quot;&gt;this answer&lt;/a&gt; to the Meta question on migration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently had a bit of a discussion with the mods over at Seasoned Advice about &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/questions/59462/my-bunn-coffeemaker-has-started-overflowing-at-the-funnel&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt; about a coffeemaker. It was posted and had &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;zero votes, zero answers, and zero other comments&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; when I suggested that it get migrated over to here at Coffee. I got push-back from my comments and ended up chatting with her (SA mod) in Chat. Her perspective was very by-the-book (i.e., the aforementioned meta) that says &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;We only migrate questions because they are off-topic on the original site. It is perfectly possible for a question to be on-topic on multiple sites, but that is not a reason to migrate it elsewhere. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a general rule&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, if someone asks a question here, and it's on-topic here, it should stay here.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(My emphasis added). I was hoping, due to context, that they'd be willing to migrate this very on-point Coffee question to Coffee.SE -- nope. I disagree &lt;em&gt;in this particular case&lt;/em&gt;, but she's a mod there and I'll respect her adherence to policy and conviction!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, migration should be &quot;uncommon&quot;. To OP's point, I think the question in question should remain here. The Coffeemaker question, I think, should have been migrated here. This may sound relativist, but we're young and can use on-point questions such as that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My opinion: If you, as an OP...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;are posting a question that is on-topic at multiple sites, and&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;are aware of both sites, and &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;choose to post it at site A instead of other sites (as @starsplusplus did in this case),&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;then I maintain that &lt;em&gt;it should not be migrated&lt;/em&gt;. If any of these assumptions are missing (e.g., OP likely doesn't know about other more-on-topic site) then it's up for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;hoc_age&lt;/code&gt; doctrine: &quot;If the question &lt;em&gt;involves coffee&lt;/em&gt;, ask it at &lt;a href=&quot;http://coffee.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Coffee.SE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastActivityDate="2015-07-30T15:10:34.817" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="1155" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2015-08-08T02:08:27.550" Score="4" ViewCount="65" Body="&lt;p&gt;I peruse both Coffee and &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Seasoned Advice&lt;/a&gt; daily. Even since the inception of the Coffee site, I frequently see coffee questions on Seasoned Advice. Coffee is on-topic at Seasoned Advice, but it's &lt;em&gt;MORE&lt;/em&gt; on-topic here!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;assume&lt;/em&gt; this is because users (new and &quot;seasoned&quot;) &lt;strong&gt;simply don't know there's a dedicated Coffee site!&lt;/strong&gt; Every time I see a coffee question on Seasoned Advice I comment on it (and sometimes answer) to encourage people to join us over here at Coffee. Some recent ones... &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/q/59711/25286&quot;&gt;this one from today&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/q/59500/25286&quot;&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt; from a few days ago that got supercollided and got an inordinate number of views... and another that spurred &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.coffee.stackexchange.com/a/1154/262&quot;&gt;this answer&lt;/a&gt; to a related MetaCoffee question. All would have been very welcome over here at Coffee! :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clearly, we're not going to migrate &lt;em&gt;previous&lt;/em&gt; SA questions about Coffee. I also understand not wanting to immediately migrate &lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt; questions because of &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackexchange.com/questions/10249/what-is-migration-and-how-does-it-work&quot;&gt;this &quot;policy&quot; (which I view more as a &lt;em&gt;suggestion&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/a&gt;; i.e., don't migrate a coffee question, because Coffee is on-topic at SA.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think this is significantly impacting Coffee.SE's adoption and relevance. If we had &lt;em&gt;all of the New Coffee Questions&lt;/em&gt; over here at Coffee, I think we'd have a much better chance of getting off the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do we get people to ask Coffee Questions here instead?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="262" LastEditorUserId="37" LastEditDate="2015-08-10T15:29:07.983" LastActivityDate="2015-08-12T17:10:14.630" Title="How can we get people to ask Coffee Questions at This Site?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;featured&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="9" />
  <row Id="1156" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1155" CreationDate="2015-08-10T15:39:26.027" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;Why limit the hunt to Seasoned Advice? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sure, they get coffee questions, and that's why you've got &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.cooking.stackexchange.com/q/2008/6728&quot;&gt;a community promotion ad&lt;/a&gt; up there. But what if we try thinking beyond &quot;where are the coffee questions and how do we get them here?&quot;, and instead, think: &quot;where are the coffee &lt;em&gt;people&lt;/em&gt; and how do we get them here?&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What kind of people are coffee Q&amp;amp;A people? Millions of people drink coffee, but what we're looking for here is coffee &lt;em&gt;hobbyists&lt;/em&gt;, not just drinkers. People who like to experiment with brewing methods, spend money on gear, and optimize for various qualities. They aren't just coffee drinkers - they're coffee &lt;em&gt;tinkerers&lt;/em&gt;. So people who might be drawn to this site are tinkerers in other fields who dabble in coffee (among many other likely hobbies). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some initial thoughts about where these kinds of people might come from:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bicycles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Beer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Homebrewing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lifehacks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Great Outdoors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are probably way more. Not all of those sites are graduated, so you won't necessarily be able to place community promotion ads, but it might be a place to start if some Coffee SE ambassadors try to make new friends in those chat rooms and see if they've got any coffee questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The upshot of this type of activity is that you aren't trying to take existing people or questions from a site that already welcomes them; you're just trying to show people who might be interested in coffee tinkering that there's a place where their questions would be welcome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My advice, in the general, tl;dr sense, would be to think about what other types of people would be likely to hang out and ask questions here (the hard part), and then figure out where to go to reach those people (the easy part). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="37" LastActivityDate="2015-08-10T15:39:26.027" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="1157" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1155" CreationDate="2015-08-10T16:08:10.803" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think you may be looking at this from the wrong angle. The purpose of creating this site &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;wasn't&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to start moving a community (or their questions) from one site to another. You're supposed to be out there on the Internet to find a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; community (or at least a new scope of questions) that were &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; being well served before. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Where is this untapped audience? Or questions that cannot be asked elsewhere? Finding them is your job now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you read my article about why (sometimes) we split off subjects from existing sites &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&quot;http://discuss.area51.stackexchange.com/a/17846/5&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apparently this is a duplicate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &amp;mdash; I list a few of the criteria we would be looking for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;We would be looking for things like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;An ecosystem of questions that are not already in scope on the existing site(s)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;A show of numbers that clearly demonstrates the parent site is failing to attract that&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  audience &lt;em&gt;&amp;larr; this is a big one&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;A weighty argument that a &lt;em&gt;new&lt;/em&gt; community exists that does not identify themselves as part of the larger subject (see &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/08/unix-and-ubuntu-why-both/&quot;&gt;Ubuntu versus Unix&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Scope Failure &amp;mdash; Maybe we got it wrong the first time. A large subject can cover a huge number of topics. But if the site is not competitive in any &lt;em&gt;particular&lt;/em&gt; subject, it &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/pruning-season/&quot;&gt;may be time for a breakup&lt;/a&gt; (&quot;sum of the parts&quot;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think (1) is a tough sell. I haven't seen many of those &lt;em&gt;&quot;largely off-topic for a cooking site&quot;&lt;/em&gt; questions yet. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, if you're trying to divert users/questions from another SE site, that disproves (2) by definition. That would have ended the creation of this site before it even got started. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That leaves (3) and (4) &amp;mdash; a community that &lt;em&gt;loves&lt;/em&gt; their coffee, but it would never occur to them to try our Cooking site. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I don't believe soliciting and diverting users from &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; SE sites is the way to go. The best way to bring in that new audience is to &lt;strong&gt;find &lt;em&gt;OTHER&lt;/em&gt; coffee communities and show them what Stack Exchange is about.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That's why we created this site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" LastEditorUserId="137" LastEditDate="2015-08-12T17:10:14.630" LastActivityDate="2015-08-12T17:10:14.630" CommentCount="4" />
</posts>